Hello and welcome back.
In this lecture, we will create the student micro service out of this university monolithic application.
So let's go for it and let's create the new springboard application.
Let's give the name is student service.
And the group come in people's cloud and the artifact is student service led, so discipline is in service
and the packages is coming up next year.
We let the mystical spring liturgy and spring web dependencies and the springboard worthiness to fall
to finish.
Let's wait for a few seconds to set up the project.
It's downloading some of the dependencies and building the project.
Now let's go to the same resources, our application properties.
And here we will put properties for database Conexant and service name and port.
So let's copy from address microsatellites all the properties in the student micro surveys.
This will remain same.
And our microcircuits name that is basically being application name is student service.
And this will run on board eight zero eight zero.
So this is the name of the application and this is the port on which it will run in our local machine.
Now let's copy packages from our monolithic application.
So this is I am going to make the things faster.
So let's copy all the packages and put inside the student micro service.
And in the.
Main class.
Let's go and additions that we have in our address service, so let me copy all because of a structure
is seen.
So this is components for controller services and entities can in repository.
Now, let's jump to our packages.
So here's what we will do.
We will remove the address entity because here we don't need anything related to address.
OK, so let's address entity because this is too micro service.
So whatever dependencies we have on the address, we need to remove.
So here we have reference to address entity with one to one mapping.
So now instead of this, we will change it to long address it.
So this will be normal.
Add column annotation and mapping.
This will be not the one to one mapping.
Now, even this is what we will not do, the mapping one-to-one, but we will map it like normal column
that we have in our student table, like we have done for our last name, email and others.
So here, let me remove this and let's go getters and setters for this field that we have address ID.
Now, we are good over here in the same way we will remove this address repository.
Now, let's jump to request so here we will not get done story density in the request.
Instead of this, we will get the address.
So this address, it will be existing in our address table.
So we are not going to create the address from this student office.
We will create the address from the address service and we will provide the address idy to our student
microsatellites.
So this will be already present in our address table.
This is basically our existing address ID in the address table.
So let me remove this and get us in status for the address ID.
The read that said, we are good over here now in the response.
So here we are getting the street and CD from the address object that we had inside our student entity
class, but just now we removed this right.
So we also need to remove this.
So here we just get those to details now, how to get the street and city basically address details
and how to map out here that we will see in the upcoming Lichter's.
For now live.
This feels like as it is and we will come to this point later.
Now, in the student service, we don't need a address repository, let's remove this and we are not
going to create the address from here, so let's remove this as well.
And here we will set the address ID.
And that we are getting in this incoming object in the form of Jason.
And then we're creating the student and we are returning back.
So we have an error in the import, let's review that as well.
We don't need to change anything in our getting the student body.
Our controller is also good.
Let's go there if we have an issue.
No, it's fine.
So this is our student microcircuits.
Now we are ready with the student service, so we'll proceed further in the next lecture.
Thank you very much.