Hello and welcome back.
Now our student and addressed micro services are ready, so here for the student, we are having the
address details.
So we need to call the address service from the student service to get the address details.
So the scenario is we need to call the address service from our student service now in Springwood to
make the right calls.
Generally, we use rest template, but from spring five onwards, it's not recommended to use race template
because Spring itself stated that in the future it will get depreciated.
So here it's recommended to use the Web client instead of rest template.
And that's what we are going to use in this class.
So to use the Web client, we need to add one dependency in the bombed out example of student service,
and that is Springwood Flux.
So make sure you are adding this dependency in the bombed out similar student service.
Now let's create the pin of Web client.
So you never mean class.
That is student service application.
Let's create one being of that client.
So.
Lynette.
Just this one from the reactive package.
Web client.
Market with at been.
Now, to make the call to address service, we need to have you are a lot better service, right?
So let's go to the application or properties of certain service and here, say a prayer service.
You are El.
Equal to localhost.
Ejiro, it, too.
This is the port on which our address, Microsoft Office, will run in our local Muzzin Sless AIPA sless
address.
So this is the you are a local address, Microsoft Office.
Now let's read this property in our main class using the add value annotation.
So that is.
Address.
Service, you are a.
Let's import it value and here.
Let's provide this property.
Now we will use this model to create the meaning of that land so that client.
Equal to the blind dot and call the metal builder here, you will see one method that is builder.
Now we need to say don't because you are right.
So we will set this one that we are reading from the application DOT properties and call the builder
matter.
So this will give us the object of the client.
Let's return it.
And this is what we are going to use throughout this student service application.
So let's have been of this web outlined in our student service.
So in this room service, let's automate this.
So using this line, we will make the rest calls to our address service.
Also, you can use this web design to make wrist calls to other services as well.
You just need to create another Benoff Web client and provider you all of that service.
So this Web client is the same kind of thing that we are using race template.
It's just that rich template is going to be deprecated and Web client is recommended to use.
So that's why we are using the Web client in the schools.
Now, in the next lecture, we will see how to use this Web client to make the rest calls.
In our example, it is called to address Microsoft Office.
So that's all for now, will proceed further in the next lecture.
Thank you very much.