Hello and welcome back.
So now we are ready with our student and address services, so let's run the both services in the local
Muzzin, so let's start the address service and student service.
Wait for a few seconds till it get started and let them do Posman, so here will hit out the student
service, getting the student by ID and past ideas one.
Now, let's call this giddap.
We got the response.
Check it out.
See, along with the student it is.
We are getting the address details as well.
The reason is that inside our student service, we are calling the address service, using the Web client
and that's what we are populating while giving back the student details in this particular model class.
And if you want to check it out, then just go to the address service logs.
And here you can see it is going inside the gate by ID.
And the idea of address is one that is basically address ID equal to one.
So here we are calling the student service and internal student service is calling the address service,
using the vaped line and that's why we are seeing these logs of address service.
So this is how our micro services can communicate with each other.
You can use this template.
If you are familiar with, then you can use Web client as well.
But there is a more efficient way and more easy way to do this as well.
And that's what we are going to do in the upcoming lectures.
So that's all for now, will proceed further in the next lecture.
Thank you very much.