Hello and welcome back.
In this lecture, we will call the address surveys from the student surveys to get the address details.
So let's go to the address surveys and inside the address, comptroller say we will call this GDP to
get the address by IDY.
So this is written in the details at Resiled Street and City.
So this will get in the former top Gissen.
So let us use the same model class from the address service to our student service.
So let me pasteboard here and let's open this, let's close this one from the address service.
Now here we don't have any declasse address and that is obvious.
We don't need this.
This is just to convert Jason to over Bojo class.
That's it.
Whatever Jason responds will get from the extra service that will convert into this particular object.
That is a stress response model class.
Now, let's go to student service.
Let me close this controller and let us use this Web line to call our address service.
So let's have a one method.
To call the address service, say we are getting a stress response.
Get addressed by ID and here we have long address ID.
Let me maximize this now, let's use that line to call the reservists of a line to get.
And we need to pass the euro.
Let's open the address controller.
So this is the euro just copied from here.
Let's get my ID.
And we have one part variable as well.
Right?
So that is ID basically address.
So here we have a tragedy.
Just can't get it.
So this is our complete you are right now, we need to call the retry matter on that and body to mono.
And provide the class, so in our example, we have a stress response, not class.
So this will return the model of a dress response, so let's sell.
Model of a dress responds.
Let me bring it down or here, let's import, so this is from the reactive package, if you see OK,
so this is a completely different topic, switching reactive.
So we are not going into that because discourse is all about micro devices with spring and spring cloud.
And this reactive part is completely a different topic.
So let's not mix up these things.
So using this more of a stress response, let's return the object of a stress response class or call
the blog matter and return it.
That's it.
So while creating the Web bean we have already provided, you are right over here, right?
So now we just need to provide this you are only or here and our part equal value.
That's it.
Now, let's call this method while getting the student details.
So inside this object, we are returning the student details.
Right.
And here we have address attributes.
So let's go object of.
Address response.
And inside that, we have at least three density, so we don't need this duplicate filter here.
Let's remove them.
And getters and setters as well.
Now, let's create getters and setters for a dress response.
Now, let's go back to the student service and here let's modify a few things quickly.
So student.
Getting the student by ID and here, let's create the new object of student response.
Like this.
Past the student.
Now, inside this student response, we need to set the address response, so let's call the response
and here we will call the matter get addressed by Eddie.
And inside this one entity class, we address ID.
We are good over here.
So what we are doing is that along with the Syrian detainees inside this glass, we are witnessing the
atrocities as well.
And for that, we are using this particular model plus from that address service.
So we are good over here.
And while creating this as well, you can do the same thing.
OK, let me copy this.
And after creating the student.
Let's have this kind of thing, let's create the new object of student order here.
And let's return this.
So after creating the student, we are returning the student details along with the address details
by getting the address details and we are calling that address service.
While getting this done by the as well, what we are doing is that we are getting the details using
this repository and we are putting the address, it is by calling the address service.
So we are all set with our student service and address service, so that's all for now, will proceed
further in the next lecture.
Thank you very much.