Hello and welcome back for the upcoming lectures, Will this spring cloud open open-faced?
Now, before we jump to that, let's first understand what is spring cloud open-faced and why we need
to use innervate spring board application.
So here Open-Faced is restraint to make the right calls.
But what spring would application?
So using the open-faced, we can make wrist calls to other services, but almost spring board application.
Other services can be our micro services or any other third party service.
It doesn't matter.
So in the previous lectures, we have seen how to use vaped line to make the calls, but a springboard
application.
So you may be thinking that why we need to go with open vein when we can do the same thing with Verplank.
So that advantage of using the open is that it's providing a declaratively and it is making our life
very easy to make the race calls from what springboard application.
Now, let me explain you the declarative method that we have in Open-Faced.
Now let's go to one controller.
So this is our controller in any of this being good applications, right.
We have Riklis mapping on the controller level and then we have different mappings.
Get mapping, Boice mapping, input, mapping.
Right.
Whatever we have.
And here we are providing the path variable or if you have any query bottoms then we use at request.
But I'm an addition.
And if you have any request payload that is coming into the request in the format of Jizan, then we
use at request buddhi annotation.
So this is declaratively we are providing that TDP matter.
We are providing that you are a part variable all with the annotations and we are using in the method.
So open pain provides the same kind of declarative metal to make the response, yes, you heard it right.
This is the steps that the consumers are calling, right.
Whatever incoming requests basically to this particular springboard application.
Now, we can have the same kind of declarative declaratively that we have in our controller to make
the race calls to other services.
It can be our own micro services or any other third party service.
We will use the same kind of annotation because then also we are making the get call or call.
We are also passing the part variable request from credit parameters.
You can see on.
We are also passing the request in or in the format up decent.
We have already seen or hear right using the reply and we are passing this.
You are right.
And this part variable and this we can do with this kind of mapping is it.
And that's what Open-Faced provides.
And this is the advantage of Sprint out of one thing.
And that's what we are going to implement in the upcoming lectures in the student service.
To make you understand that, why, Open-Faced, we need to use we have already implemented this wetland
so that you will get the idea that how open open-faced makes our life very easy and you can easily compare
vaped lined with open fields.
So this is an overview of open field.
And in the upcoming lectures, we will use the open field in our student service to make the rest calls
to address service.
So that's all for now.
Will proceed further in the next lecture.
Thank you very much.