Hello and welcome back.
In this lecture, we will have an overview of our university monolithic application.
So in the upcoming lectures, we will create the micro services out of this university monolithic application.
But before that, let's have a quick overview of this monolithic application.
So this is a springboard application, and I'm using the version as two for two.
This is the latest version.
When I'm recording this lecture, you can use the latest version, whatever is available when you are
watching this lecture.
And here we have a couple of dependencies.
This is Web dependency because our monolithic application is having the right steps and spinning data
to connect our MySQL database.
We will use the data to connect to our MySQL database and we have Mystikal Connector.
And that's obvious because we are going to connect to MySQL database from our spring boot application.
Now let's go to the application properties.
So this is having the properties to connect over MySQL database that is running in our local machine
on board three three zero six and the schema is university.
Now, let's turn to our coding part.
So here we have our main class.
So this is another tidbit at Springwood application, we have components for our controller and service
packages.
We have this and it is going to scan our GPS and it is and one package for our GPS repository.
So we have enabled Gibeah repositories as well.
Now for the rest, because obviously we need some model classes or you can support your classes.
Right, for the request and response.
So here we have one model class to create that student.
So it's having some feel for the student to create.
So this is basically our design that we are going to pass as request payload and we are returning the
student details using this model class back to the consumer with hitting our three steps.
So this will get converted into the Gissen.
Here we have a repository for address and student and we have ended classes.
So this is addressing entity class map to arrestable that we have in our database and map the corresponding
columns.
And here is our student entity, class map to student table.
And we have one to one mapping from our student to address entity because we have a relationship between
student and address table that we have in our school database.
Now, let's go to the controller to look at the apps that we have.
So here we have two apps.
First is to create the second, and the second is to get the student by now here while creating the
student.
We will get the request details in this model class and we'll pass it to overservice later.
Here we are first inserting into the address table and we are obtaining the primary job at this table
and then we are inserting the new recording to the student table.
So this is a very simple operation to create the student along with the address details here we are
using the address in student repository.
Now, our second option is to get this done by Idy.
And here we are using student repository to find the student body and using this model.
Plus we are returning back to the consumer in the format of Jason.
So this is very basic springboard application.
You can see having the dependencies, the properties to connect to MySQL database using this data and
Kappelhoff configuration controller in services.
Now let's run this monolithic application.
Wait for it.
Now let's turn to paceman.
So here, the student able to get the student by ID, so let's see, we got the student details were
added equal to one along with the address details.
So here we are, good with our monolithic application that is universally monolithic application.
Now, in the upcoming lectures, we will create the micro services out of this monolithic application.
So here we are going to create two micro services out of this monolithic application.
One is addressed micro service, and second is student micro service.
So that's what we are going to do in the upcoming lectures.
You will get this university application along with this lecture.
So download the source code and importing your ideas and just have a look, because this is very simple,
good application.
So that's all for now.
Will proceed further in the next lecture.
Thank you very much.