Hello and welcome to Discourse, first of all, thank you so much for taking this course before we start
building micro services with spring board and spring cloud.
Let me give you a sort introduction to the calls.
The very first thing is for structure, this course is all about building micro services with spring
board and spring cloud.
So first you will learn what is monolithic application and how to create micro services out of your
monolithic application.
This goes a step by step tutorial to build a micro services with spring board and spring cloud.
Someone has rightly said that don't judge a book by its cover and the same thing is applicable for discourse,
discourse is having four hours of content.
So I would like to request you, what, at least 30 to 50 percent of the calls and then come up with
your constructive feedback?
I'm always looking for the constructive feedback to improve the quality.
The next phase of the course, some students referred to learning speed, and some students prefer to
learning slow speed in this course.
I tried my best to keep the medium pace targeting all kind of students whenever required.
I slow down my pace to make you understand the topic in a better way.
Still, if you think that pace of the course is fast or slow, then in the video player you have option
to either increase or decrease the speed.
Source code and other resources that we are going to use in this course that we will find inside the
lectures and you can download them as well.
English is not my mother tongue, so I hope before taking the course, you have watched the previous
videos to take my teaching style and English pronunciation.
Yeah, that's the introduction to the cause, and from next lecture, we will start our journey up micro
services with Springwood and Sprinklered.