Hello and welcome back.
In this lecture, we will download and set up JDK apartment and spring tools in our local Muzzin.
So first, let's go with.
That is our development kit and this is the official website of Oracle, and from here you can download
the dedicate in this cause I'm going to use it, which is coming at free cost by Oracle because this
is our personal and development use or you can say educational use.
If you want to use Harverson, then get it, you can go with open Jadeja that is coming under the open
source license.
So it's up to you in this course.
I'm going to use it.
So download adjudicate according to your operating system, Linux, Windows, or make it up to you.
So download and install in your local machine.
Now the next thing is to do so.
In this course we are going to use the Apache Marwin.
If you are familiar with Criddle, you can go for it as well.
So this is the official website of the bottom of it.
And from here you can download the Apache, Marvin, whatever it was and you can see you can go for
it.
So download according to your operating system and install in your local machine.
The next thing is Idy, you can go with Eclipse the idea, and that means whatever you prefer, it's
up to you in this cause I'm going to use Steer's that is spring tonsured.
So this is the official website of ideas.
And here you can download these ideas according to your operating system, Linux, Mac or Windows.
It's up to you.
If you are familiar with the intelligencia and you want to go for it, it's up to you in this course,
I'm going to use the ideas.
So I would recommend download and install ideas in your local machine from the official website of Stass.
So download and install these three softwares in your local machine, according to your operating system,
after downloading and installing, if you are a Windows user, then search for the environment variables.
And here you see system environment variables.
In that one step, you will see environment variables.
So here we need to create two new environment variables.
The first is a home, which is basically part over JDK and the name is Dullahan, and this is the path
to JDK.
Whatever is in your local machine, at what location it is being installed and make sure you are not
giving the Bindaree in this part.
Only you need to get.
The second is home to home.
The name is M2M and this is where your apartment is installed and make sure you are not giving the bin
directly in the path.
So up to creating these two new environment variables, the next thing is we need to send in the existing
part environment variable so this will be already exist in your machine.
So just edit it and put your two environmental variables like this person, date home, percentage lesbian
and same for your marine part, came to homes lesbian.
So this is all you need to do, download JDK, Apache, Mudvayne and SD and install them after that,
create the two environment variables and set those in your party environment variable like this.
So make sure you are doing this before we start the next lecture.
So that's all for now, will proceed further in the next lecture.
Thank you very much.