Hello and welcome back.
In this lecture, we will download and install music in our local machine.
In this course, we are going to use music as the database connecting to our Springwood application.
So here is the official website of my school.
Just go over here and download the music world according to your operating system.
So this includes my school server and my second workbench MySQL server is required because we are going
to run the database in our local machine and to execute the queries on that server, we need UI that
is my workbench to execute the queries.
So download and install, according to your operating system, after installing it, if you are a Windows
user, then go inside your program files.
You will see this folder being created.
MiSeq will go inside the physical server inside the bin.
Here you will see one that is mythically to start the mystical server in our local machine.
We need to run this file so it does Double-Click, and it will start the physical server in our local
machine.
If this is not working for you, then there is another option as well, the search for the services
and inside the services go for Mystikal.
You see or hear just right, click and start.
So this will start the sequel server in our local machine, if you check the properties, it is pointing
to only my second or the lose.
That's what we just now seen.
So now my second story is running in our local machine, so let's connect to it using my second workbench,
so open the bicycle workbench.
And you need to make the connection.
Localhost, you can you can name anything hostis localhost, this is the by default port for the local
bicycle, Sawatari three 06 Rudie the username and password.
Whatever you give during the installation, click on the disconnection test is successful.
So we are good to go here.
Just click on here to connect to local database.
So here are the default schemas provided by bicycle.
That's fine as we proceed in the course, we will create another schema for our micro services.
So make sure before the next lecture you download and install music in your local machine, so that's
all for now, will proceed further in the next lecture.
Thank you very much.