Hello and welcome back for the upcoming lectures, we are going to focus on the spring cloud EPA Gateway.
So before we jump to the implementation, let's first understand what is EPA gateway and why we need
it.
Now, here we have two micro services.
One is student service and another one is a service.
Now, consumer will hit these micro services by having the wall of these micro services.
Now say we want to implement authentication in our micro services, so what we need to do is that we
need to implement separately in each of our micro services.
So that's the repetition of the code.
And if we have a slight change and we have thousands of micro services, then we need to changing all
the micro services.
So that's a big task.
Another thing is that we want to log the request and response for all the micro services.
So these are the crosscutting concerns.
So if we want to achieve this in the centralized place, then here comes the API gateway.
So here it is, the middle man, and this is basically a separate springboard application.
And so, for example, it's running on the Port nine zero nine zero in local Muzzin.
So now what will happen, whatever requests are coming from our consumer, will first come to Gateway.
Now EPA Gate will withdraw that particular request to the appropriate Microsoft B student service or
address service.
It is the responsibility of EPA Gateway to Rouda request to particular Microsoft Office.
So now here what will happen, we will not set over Microsoft with you orders to the consumer, instead
of that, we will give them the you are a low power gateway.
So what will happen?
Consumer will hit this.
You are.
That is the gateway.
And let's take one example how the routing happens.
So, for example, consumer wants to hit the student service so it will hit the You are Telopea Gateway
localhost nine zero nine zero service name Synagis student service as opposed to done less get by ID.
So this is the are that consumer will hate, and in the end, it will provide the name of the service
now EPA, yet we will allow that request to our student service and student service will give the response
back to EPA and EPA, yet we will give that response back to the consumer.
So this is the complete flaw for our request and response when we have EPA gateway in the picture.
Now, the question is how the EPA gateway will allow the request to the appropriate micro service.
And the answer is sprinklered.
Eureka.
Because we know.
Right.
Utica is having all the details for our all the micro services.
It's having all the instanced it is for each of our Microsoft is along with the others.
So what will happen?
Sprinklered.
EPA Gateway will work with the Utica to put out the request to appropriate microcircuits, which request
which are coming from the consumer.
Now, let's talk about the crosscutting concerns.
So, for example, consumer eating over microcircuits.
So what will happen first?
The request will come to EPA Gateway.
So here we can implement the authentication.
If Authentications is successful, then API Gateway will allow that request to appropriate microcircuits.
Otherwise API Gateway will give the response back to the consumer that is basically in error.
Another thing you want to have is that you want to add the header to your request before the EPA get
without the request to particular Microsoft Office.
So this is you can do with the help of three filter.
So now our Microsoft Office will give the response back to API Gateway.
And here we want to add some response header before the API gateway gives the response back to consumer.
Or we want to log the response, whatever you want to.
How so?
This you can do with the help of post filter so prefilled.
That means before the API gateway around the request to appropriate Microsoft Office and post filter
means before the API gateway gives the response back to the consumer.
So with the help of pre and post filters, you can have crosscutting concerns in the EPA gateway.
So you don't need to implement logging or say, for example, authentication in each of the micro services
in one place, you will put and it will be applicable for all your micro services.
So, for example, in the future, you are adding new micro service.
So you don't need to worry about the authentication because you have authentication in the API gateway.
So this will take care.
The authentication for newly added micro service as well.
Now, let's talk about load balancing, so here I get we will do the load balancing as well.
So, for example, we have to instant's for our student service said, for example, consumer resiting
student service using the You are Telopea Gateway.
Now, it will divide the load across all the instances for student service.
And this is applicable for all of our micro services.
So here it period, we will do the load balancing across all the instances we have for that particular
micro service.
So this is an overview of a period and in the upcoming lectures, we will see the implementation of
Spring Cloud API Gateway.
So that's all for now, will proceed further in the next lecture.
Thank you very much.