Hello and welcome back.
In this lecture, we will create the API Gateway application, so that is basically a springboard application.
So let's create the new springboard application.
And give the name is Epper Gateway.
Provide the group as common as Cloud Artefact, a gateway server API gateway.
This is the package we want to click on the next.
Now, to add the gateway dependency, just search for Gateway and add this dependency, Solier Spring
was providing a gateway that is all, but now it's in the maintenance more.
So we are going to use the latest one.
That is Spring Cloud API Gateway.
So select this one now.
But it'd be a gateway application will use the Eureka server to allow the request to appropriate service.
So for that we need to register our API Gateway application to Eureka server.
So for that, we need to add the Eureka discovery line to this Gateway application.
Now just click on the next and finish.
Now, let's open the application properties of our EPA, get the application.
So first thing we will said the Salvador report is nine zero nine zero, because we are going to run
this EPA Goodway application on board nine zero nine zero one local Muzzin.
Now, the next is application nine.
The EPA gateway.
Now we need to register this gateway application to Eureka server so that we know, right, what we
need to do in the main class, we need to annotate with enable.
Yurick, our client.
And we need to provide that you are a of Eureka server application DOT properties file, so let's copy
it from one of our micro services.
So let me copy this, you are a Eureka server and provide what here?
So this is what we have done, we created the EPA get the application, we set the port application
name and we registered it with Eureka Server by providing you all of Eureka.
And we enable it in our meaningless.
Now, furthermore, the configuration we will see in the next lecture, so that's all for now, will
proceed further in the next lecture.
Thank you very much.