Hello and welcome back.
So now we are all set with our spring cloud getaway.
So let's start with the Eureka server and then we will start the gateway.
And after that, we will start our micro services to run my groceries and now address Microsoft Office.
Lets them do Eureka.
Let's reload this.
EPA gateway has registred.
Wait for the migrant services.
Yes, now we are good, our micro services, along with the EPA, we have registered themselves with
the Utica now lets them do the postman.
So now we have used this, you are allowed to hate our student service because of a student service
is running on the board a zero eight zero, and now we are not going to use this.
You instead of this, we will use the you are not Ed Gateway.
And we know that Be Gateway is running on the point nine zero nine zero.
And then we need to provide the name of service.
So in our case, student service.
Now, let's get idea.
See, we got the response, so this you are we hit up Gateway, but actually we are down student service,
but we are not using the you are a student service.
Earlier we were using the you are a student service, but now we are using the you are an up gateway
to hit our student service.
Now, it may be possible that when you hit this giddap right, or any other Epper, you will get four
zero four.
That's obvious.
Don't worry.
Give the EPA, get the application a minute and then try again.
Because what happens when you start to appreciate the application, right.
It will affect all the services from the Eureka server.
So this will take some time.
Sometimes it may be 30 seconds to one minute.
So don't worry.
Wait for a minute and then try again.
So now this is the you are all for our student service and this you are all you need to provide to your
consumers, not this one.
That is the actual you are all of your student service localhost.
Ejiro, Ed, you should not give this you out to your consumers.
Instead of that, you need to give that you all of your EP Gateway and slash your microscopist name.
So now here, Ippei Gateways routing this particular gate request to our student service and hence we
are getting the response and this is expected.
We have already seen.
So this is how you can use sprinklered, cloud, API, gateway for your micro services along with your
Akazawa.
So that's all for now, will proceed further in the next lecture.
Thank you very much.