Hello and welcome back.
In this lecture, we will create the post filter now here using the statement API get to withdraw the
request to appropriate Microsoft Microcircuits.
Now post filter will get executed after our micro service gives the response back to API Gateway and
before our API gateway passes that response to the consumer.
So that's the in-between state.
You can see now here to have the possibility that we will use the Lamela.
So let's modify like this then and use the model.
D'Arte from Runnable and using the Labrada, let's the post filter like this.
Now, here, whatever we decide that will be ever possible that we can do anything, whatever we want
to do, just before I get passes, the response back to consumer, say, for example, we want to be
responsible.
Right.
About Microsoft is giving the response.
So we want to log what is the response called entity B response would basically be to interrogate for
over 500 internal server, whatever it is.
Right.
We want to log that response code.
So here we will use this object of exchange.
So exchange dot, get a response.
And here.
Server, ATP Response.
Let's import the Sahuarita response from this one.
Now let's log the ATP status code, so Lowgar Dot info.
Post filter equal to.
Response get.
Status quo.
That's it.
So this is our first filter, so we have one debate point over here.
Let's one other point out here.
Now let's run our API, get replication in debug mode and UDCA server and other micro services are already
running.
Ignore this one.
So we have to debug points out here, one port filter, one port and another one in our student service.
So let's have Unica.
Yeah, that's running fine.
Let's say this, Gadsby.
So execution came over here.
That is our prefill done, let me clear the logs, but before that, let's take over here, see authorities
and equal the ABC.
So let's not clear the logs.
Just click on David.
Now we are inside the room service.
And let's go to the logs of EPA Gateway.
Just click on David.
See the execution game in our post filter and still we don't have a response to our request and let's
do it.
See the possibility equal to 200, OK, so this is our filter, then the request is going into the service
and then coming back to our post filter and after that, a bigot is giving the response back to the
consumer who is hitting over Epis.
Now, let's go back to our filters, so this filter will be executed for all the requests coming to
our all micro services.
Now say, for example, you want to have some specific code for only some of the services or any particular
service.
So, for example, we want to have some specific condition inside of a pre filter for student service.
Only then how we can add to that.
Let's see that part as well.
So here we will put one condition like this, that request.
Not get you, are I?
Two string, and it contains Sless API.
Student.
Then do something, whatever you want to have for the student microcircuits, you can put this piece
of Cawdor here or whatever, so this will be applicable to only student service.
Likewise, you can have other conditions for your address service or for any other micro service.
So this will be specific to particular service, if you put conditions like this using the part of a
particular micro service, otherwise this will get executed.
But all the requests coming to your all micro services and same applies for our post request.
This will get executed for all requests coming to our all micro services.
So this is how you can have crosscutting concerns in the API gateway using pre and post filter, so
that's all for now, will proceed further in the next lecture.
Thank you very much.