Hello and welcome back.
In the previous lecture, we have seen how to use the paint lined along with the EPA gateway to call
the service from our student service.
Now, if you remember that in one of the previous lecture, we have created this load balancer while
calling the address service from our student service.
But now in England, we are using the EPA gateway.
We are not directly calling the address service and we know that EPA gateway is doing the load balancing
for us.
So now we don't need this load balancer.
So let's comment it out and let's test the load.
Balancing is working or not.
So let's start with the Utica server.
Then the EPA gateway.
Will start the student service and the first instance of a service on board, a donate to the second,
we will start on board a derogatory.
So this is a druidry led to the second instance of a dress service, give this some time because I get
when your server is working, we can take over here.
We have a good restaurant service, let's wait for the address service.
We have one instance of better service.
Let's wait for another one.
Yeah, now we are all set a disservice to instances.
We have epic adventure in service.
Now, let's clear the logs for our address service here.
This is first instance.
This is second.
Let's clear the logs.
Now let's turn to Posman.
And hit this giddap.
This is fantastic.
This will hit three more.
This is second, third and now fourth.
We are all set.
Let's take the logs.
Let's move to address service.
This is the first instance seek to request here now in the second instance.
Toward here, so it'd be a good way of doing the load, balancing across the two instances of our adversaries,
and the reason is that now we are using the EPA get wind of being light and using this line.
We are calling the service from our student service.
So we don't need to worry about the load balancing.
Basically, we don't need to have our own implementation for clean side load balancing if we are using
EPA to be.
So now you got the idea that we will do the load balancing for us and we don't need to worry about it,
so that's all for now, will proceed further in the next lecture.
Thank you very much.