Hello and welcome back.
So now we know that our API Gateway application will work with Unica Server to allow the request to
appropriate Microsoft Office, but for that, we need to configure it.
So let's enable the discovery locator for our API Gateway application.
So we need to set properties.
Spring cloud.
Gateway.
That discovery locator enabled a call to prove.
Now, let's go to the Eureka server here, you see the application name in the press, but if we actually
look in the application, the properties of our micro service, then we have provided in the lowercase.
But Yanagisawa is residing in the upper case.
So we need to tell this to our API Gateway application that look for the micro services in lowercase.
So for that, we need to define the property in our gateway application as.
Out cloud.
Gateway thought this Cody locator and then lower case service I'd call to through.
So now even the Utica server is providing the service name in the upper case to over a period of application,
it will look for the Lorqess service name or you can say service ID.
You can read this documentation as well, what it is saying.
Option to Lorqess, the service that pretty useful with Unica when it automatically abacuses service
idee or you can say application mean or you cancel service name.
So my service would magids less my service from uppercase to Lorqess.
I don't know, for some reason, this is giving Iran even we provided a boolean value, so we will ignore
this.
So this is the configuration we need to do and now we are ready with our Epper Gateway application.
So in the next lecture, we will test it out.
So that's all for now.
Will proceed further in the next lecture.
Thank you very much.