Hello and welcome back for the upcoming lectures, we are going to create Brief Elter and Poolesville
in our EPA Gateway application.
Using these filters, you can have some cost cutting concerns in the EPA gateway like you want to authenticate
the request.
You want to log the request or do you want to log the response or response code?
Whatever you want to do, you can do using the pre and post filter and have your crosscutting concerns
in the API Gateway application.
In this lecture, we will create the prefilled.
So this will get executed before the EPA gets around the request to appropriate microcircuits.
So here we can do authentication or we can log the requests, whatever we want to do.
So let's go for it.
Let's create a new class.
And the name is Custom Filter.
Let's mark this closet at configuration and let's have one longer for this.
Plus.
Logger factory.
Get longer and you diskless over here.
Let me maximize this.
Let's import the logger now here.
We need to implement global filter provided by EPA Gateway so implements global filter.
So this is coming from the EPA.
You see here, this is the package.
Now we need to write the metal.
Let me read you this comment.
Now, this pre filter will be applicable to all the requests coming to our all micro services, Nowzad,
for example, for all our requests.
That is one header coming in, the request, for example, authorization and that we want to log.
Let's go for it.
So what we will do here is that using this exchange object, let's call the mattress, get requests.
So this will return server.
Its GDP request and make sure you are selecting this reactive.
So.
Linguistical to.
So now we have the request, right, so let's lock the authorities in attitude coming in the header.
So Lowgar Todd.
Info say authorisation equal to and here request to get headers, not get first and pass the header.
So say for example, we are passing the header in the request.
So now here we are just logging the authorities an attribute coming in the request.
But you can actually perform the authentication if you want.
Now, instead of returning the null, what we need to do is that we need to put out this request to
appropriate microsatellites because that's the actual means of epigraphy, right?
So we cannot return null.
So instead of that, we need to return gene dot filter and past object of exchange.
So this will pass the request to appropriate microcircuits.
And before that, we can do whatever we want to have authentication or whatever.
So this is our printer and then we are routing the request to appropriate microcircuits.
Now, see, for example, here you are getting the authorization and that is failing, then you can
straighten it out better and pass that along to the consumer, you will not allow the request to microcircuits.
If authentication is successful, you can rouda the request to the appropriate medical service otherwise
through the error to consumers that you are not authenticated.
Now, this is our filter and in the next lecture we will test it out.
So that's all for now.
Will proceed further in the next lecture.
Thank you very much.