Hello and welcome back.
Now we are all set with our pre filter, so let's test it out.
But before that, let's put one point in our filter or here and one point in our student controller.
So this is inside our student service.
Now, first, we need to start the Eureka server and we will start the EPA gateway in debug mode and
also student service in the department.
And let's start the address service.
Ignore this error.
Let's start the service and wait for few seconds.
Let's jump to Eureka.
So just now, get with your let's reload.
Now we are all set, let's jump to both men and this is our goodbye for this one.
So in the headlines, we will put authorities on.
See, the value is ABC.
OK, just let me tell you, I am passing now on the same.
Let's go to see here it is coming and let's check the logs for our Epper Gateway, what we are seeing.
So we have type over here authorization, so let's correct it out, this one.
What here and here as well.
Let's ignore this one.
Let's stop the EPA gateway.
Let's start it, we are gaining the department.
This was the typo, so ignore it.
Let's turn to Eureka and see if we are all good.
Yes, now let's hit this request again.
And let's take the logs.
We are getting the ABC see now just click on the effort to pass the request to next point.
Now we are getting into the student service, you see the control coming to this particular gate mapping
that is inside our student service now.
Just click on the effort.
We got the response here.
So what we did over here is that we have this briefing tour before the EPA gets around the request to
our students.
So this is our three filter.
Now, in the next lecture, we will see the post filter.
So that's all for now.
Will proceed further in the next lecture.
Thank you very much.