Hello and welcome back.
So now we know that whatever requests are coming from the consumer will first come to EPA Gateway,
but how about the internal calls that are going between our Microsoft offices?
So, you know, example, student service is calling the address service and here student service is
directly calling the address service, using this name with the help of Eureka server.
We have already seen that.
Right.
But what if we want to make this call?
Also went through the API gateway.
So that means student service will call the EPA, Gateway and EPA Gateway will pass that request to
the service.
And here at the service will give the response to EPA, Gateway and EPA to attend, will pass that response
back to the student service.
So to add to that, we need to do slight modifications involving client, and that's what we are going
to do in this lecture.
So let's jump to Estes.
So this is our address fenland, right?
We have already seen so here we have provided the name of the service as a service.
So now we should not be doing this.
And let's put the name of the service here and here.
We need to provide the name for our API application.
So that is Gateway.
Now, if we do this kind of thing, then what will happen, we can be able to just call the address
micro service using the EPA because you cannot create another front line with the value equal to EPA
gateway.
So now we should not be using the pot like this.
So let's remove from here and invite every request we should be doing like this.
So now this address for England is no longer specific to address microcircuits, this being land we
can use to call our any of micro services, and that is to using the EPA gateway so we can rename this
for England as well.
But let's leave it like this only.
But you need to understand one thing that now this is no longer specific to address Microsoft.
With this being blind, you can use to call any of your micro offices and that call will go through
the API gateway for every you get call or any other call you are making to any of your micro services.
You need to first provide the name of the service and then you are mapping like this.
So now we are all set.
So we will start with the Eureka server, then our API gateway.
Student surveys and address surveys now wait for few seconds till then, let's jump to Bowsman.
Let's hit this again.
No problem, wait for a few more seconds.
We are getting word that sometimes happens with the.
No need to worry about it.
Let's try again.
So now we got a response, so this is obvious, but now this call from the student service to address
service to get this address dated is going through the EPA gate with this.
We are not calling directly to address service.
Instead of that, what we are doing from our student service, we are calling the EPA gateway and that
to using the Utica server, because you see or hear we have given the service name for our gateway application,
and that is EPA gate, which you can verify in our Utica survey residency.
This is the name of our service for the EPA Gateway application.
So by this way, your internal calls between micro services can also pass through the EPA gateway and
your crosscutting concerns, whatever you have in the EPA gateway will get executed.
You can verify the EPA gateway logs as well.
So let's jump to logs of EPA, get replication.
See here we have to pre filter for one outrageous and is fine ABC.
This is for the filter of request going from Sudan to address service.
And for that, obviously, we don't have any authorization requested.
And you see these two possibilities.
One, for our student request that we are getting from the postman.
And this is second, when to address service, giving the response back to EPA Gateway.
And that's the reason that our filters and filters will get executed two times in this particular scenario,
because now the call from student service to address surveys is going through the EPA gateway and hands
of a crosscutting concerns whatever we have in the EPA gate, we will get executed.
So this is how you can use your faint lined with the EPA gateway.
So that's all for now, will proceed further in the next lecture.
Thank you very much.