Hello and welcome back for the upcoming lectures, we are going to focus on the blind side load balancing.
So for clients, I'd load balancing spring provides spring cloud load balancer, and that's what we
are going to implement in the upcoming lectors.
But before that, let's first understand what is Clydeside load balancing and why we need it.
So we know these are the micro services, we have student and address service.
So, for example, the two instances where our address service, one running on the Ejiro to port and
the other one is running on the port.
Ejiro, 80.
Now, we know, for example, student service is making the right call to address service.
For example, there are a thousand requests per second going from the student service to address service.
So what will happen if all the thousand requests will go to this particular instance, which is running
on the point eight zero eight two?
It will obviously slow down the performance of this instance.
Right.
So for this particular instance, it will be hard to handle this many requests per second.
So obviously, Edra service will take some more time to respond back to student service.
Now, on the other hand, this instance, which is running on the Port, Ejiro, 83, is the ideal and
doing nothing.
So thousand requests are going to this instance, but nothing is going on this particular instance.
So this is not what we wanted to have.
Right.
We want to help load balancing between these two instances.
Hundred requests coming from student service to address service is called as load number of requests
coming.
Right.
So what we want to have is that 500 requests should go to this particular instance and another five
requests would go to this particular instance, which is running on the port a 083.
So here we are balancing the load across all the instances of the particular micro service.
So this is load balancing our requests coming is you can see his load and we are balancing across all
the instances for our micro service here.
We have to we can have three, five, 10 instances for our micro services.
So dividing total load, total request coming to our Miklós service across all the instances, we are
calling it as load balancing.
Now, here, a student service is calling the address service so we can say that student services on
that line site and if we implement this load balancing in the student service, then we can see it as
blindsight load balancing.
And for that, spring provides spring cloud load balancer.
Now we know that we are having the Eureka server, so each of our micro surveys will register itself
with the Eureka server, so that part we have already seen.
So here, what happens to that micro service with the help of Eureka server will identify that there
are two instances of address service.
And now using the cloud load balancer, it will divide the request, basically the load across the instances
of the address service.
In our case, we have two instances.
Port address service.
So the law that basically the request will get divided across these two instances, 500 will go to this
one and another 500 will go to this one, and that will be done using the help of spring cloud load
balancer along with Udei Castevet.
So here the spring cloud load balancer follows the Round-Robin matter.
So, for example, there are four requests per second going from the student surveys to address surveys.
So what will happen?
The first request will go to this instance, which is running on the way to the second will go on this
one again.
The third one will go to the first, this one and fourth will go to this particular instance and it
will repeat again.
So this is Round-Robin here.
We have two instances.
So, for example, if we have three instances, then what will happen?
The first request will go to first node, or you can say first instance, the second will go to second,
third will go to third and again, fourth will go to first instance.
Now, we know that in the student service, we are using the open phone to call the address service,
so we need to implement the spring cloud load balancer in the student service along with the spring
cloud open-faced.
And that's what we are going to do in the upcoming lectures.
We need to configure our open screen along with the spring cloud load balancer so that we can achieve
the client side load balancing in our student service while calling our address micro service.
Atleo sprinklered was providing the ribbon, but now it's being deprecated and we are not going to use
that incident that we are going to implement, the latest one that is bringing cloud load balancer.
So this is the client side load balancing and why we need it and how to implement this in our micro
services.
That's what we are going to start from the next lecture.
So that's all for now.
Will proceed further in the next lecture.
Thank you very much.