Hello and welcome back.
In this lecture, we will configure our faint line to achieve the client side load balancing in the
student service support that we need to add this dependency in the bombed out example of student service.
And the dependency is spinning loud starter load balancer.
So make sure you are adding this dependency in the bombed out example of your student service.
Now to make the rest call from student service to address service, we have the faint line and that
is address faint line.
We have already seen this right and using the Eureka server, we are providing the service name or here.
So now let's configure this vent line to use the spring cloud load balancer.
So here, let's create a new class for the configuration.
Let me give the name as address service.
Load balancer config I'm giving in the short form.
Click on the Finniss.
Now we need to annotate this class with the load balancer client.
Now, in England, we have provided this value, right?
That is the name of the service.
So same thing we need to provide with this annotation as well so that it will identify that this is
the load balancer for this particular faint client.
So make sure you are giving the same value as you have in your phone line.
So in our case, this is the name of the service because we are using the Eureka server.
So now what happens when we will start the student service?
It will create the Benoff front line, so at the time we need to configure the load balancing.
So what we will do here is that let's create the being of Fien.
Dart builder, see?
Famed builder.
Let's return.
Fiend, art builder, this matter.
So this is the being we are creating in our student service will start now here we need to tell that
we want to have load balancing.
So mark this with at Lower Peninsula.
So what will happen when we will start our student service?
It will configure this vein builder.
At the time we are seeing that this is load balancer and for which ringland?
That is what we provided here with the value.
This is for the service and for that we have this address front line.
So what will happen?
Whenever you will use the instance of this address being lined, it will get load balancer.
It doesn't matter where you are using here we are using in the student service so that also it will
get automatically load balancer.
If you are using in any of the other packages or other classes you are using the instance of this particular
line, it will automatically get lower peninsula here if you open.
Here, we don't need to change anything, we don't need to change anything, just our class where we
are configuring and providing the name of the service.
In our case, we have a service and we are saying that this is load bearing the faint line.
That's it.
This is all you need to do to configure the sprinklered load balancing in your student service.
Now we are all set with our client and spring cloud load balancer.
We will test it out in the next lecture.
So that's all for now.
Will proceed further in the next lecture.
Thank you very much.