Hello and welcome back.
So now we are all set with our faint light and spring cloud load balancer, so let's test it out.
So first we will start the Eureka server.
Now, let's start the student service and let's start the first instance of our adversaries on the board
of eight zero eight two.
Now, the second instance will start on the Port Ejiro entry, so let's again run the address service,
so that will start on the port of entry.
We can verify that on the Eureka server.
So let's open the Eureka server.
Still, we just have one instance of a delay to.
Let's reload.
Let's give a moment, yeah.
Now we have two incidents what address service?
The one is running on the port Ejiro and another one is running on the port of entry.
And we have one instance for our student service that is running on the boat, eight zero eight zero.
Now we have two instance for our address service, so how we will test it out.
We are going to hit our student service, that is get student by ID.
So internal student service is calling the address service.
And in the address service, we have this long statement.
So using this long statement, we can come to know that how many requests came to particular instance
for the address service.
So we will utilize this long statement.
So let me maximize the logs, and this is one instance of that reservist.
Let me clear the logs and this is another one.
Let me clear the logs.
Now, let's see.
This is the first request to our service.
This is second and the third one.
So total three request to our student service and internally, three requests from student service to
address service now in the logs.
Let's check it out.
So here for this instance, we can see that one request came for this particular instance of better
service.
And for this one, let's see, talking, OK, two plus one, three total.
Now, let's hit the fourth request over student service and let's see where it goes.
Here we have two it remains in.
And in this one, you see from one now we can see that the fourth request came to this particular instance,
so we hit a portal for request and internally for requests from student service to address service.
So to request came to this particular instance and to request went to this particular instance.
So it got loaded across all the instances we have for address service.
So this is all done with the help of Eureka server, open phone line and sprint cloud load balancer,
because by this registry student service will identify that there are two instances of address service
and we have already done the configuration in our student service.
Let's go over there.
This is the front line and this is our configuration that load balance TUFFIN client for the address
service.
So here we have done the load balancing using the sprint cloud load balancer, but we took the advantage
of Eureka server and faint light and that's the beauty of spring cloud.
So this is how you can achieve clydeside load balancing for your micro services using sprint cloud load
balancer, so that's all for now, will proceed further in the next lecture.
Thank you very much.