Hello and welcome back.
Before we jump to micro services, let's first understand what is monolithic application.
Maybe you are aware of monolithic application or it may be possible that you are working on the application,
which is monolithic, but you don't know that this is called a monolithic.
Now, here to understand this, let's take the example of a university application.
So in this application, we can have different components, like for the university.
We have students and certain details like address or the subjects that the student is learning and the
how different faculties in the university like commerce, arts, engineering, medical, pharmacy and
many more.
For the university, we have professors and we also have non-academic staff as well with doing office
work and for the university we have online examination portal by which university is taking the online
examination.
And we have one result component by which university is providing results to the students across all
the faculties.
There are more components also possible like liability and any other, but here, let's concentrate
on these six components for this particular example.
So this all six components or whatever, you have twenty or twenty five, if you have all these components
in the single application, then it is called this monolithic application.
So all the components in a single spring would application.
You can say that it is monolithic application.
Now, this is gender term.
So here I am taking example of Springwood because this course is all about micro services with springboard
and spinning cloud.
But this is applicable to any of the programming languages and any of the web frameworks that you are
using.
Now, let's talk about the drawbacks of the monolithic application.
The first is called complexity, as you have just one single application, you will have a lot of packages,
controllers and entity classes inside that.
So as a developer, it will be very hard to go through all the thousands lines of code and different
packages.
And another thing is, say, for example, you have a slight change in one component.
For example, in result component.
Then you need to test complete application because you have all the components in just one Springwood
application.
Now, here we just have six.
But when you have actual application in hand, you might be having 20, 50 or 100 components within
the same Springwood application.
So as a developer, it is very hard to understand the business logic.
The next is tight coupling between the different components.
So, for example, if your application is down, then none of your components will be accessible by
the end user.
So, for example, your application is down, then student registration is going on.
That will be also down if some faculty work is going on, on the examination portal or result, that
will not be accessible because you have all the things in just one application.
You cannot access other components while your application is down.
So that is tight coupling between your components.
The authorities scalability.
So when the academic year starts, right, you have usurers, for example, huge traffic for the student
registration and your examination and research portal doesn't have that much traffic at that time.
So obviously, you need to increase the competition power.
Basically, you need to upgrade the server or you need to scale your application.
You need to have more instances for your Springwood application to handle that traffic for the student
registration.
So increasing the competition power or increasing the number of instances is basically cost.
You are going to pay for that.
Now, the same happens when you have examinees and for the university, right?
Lot of students are giving the examinees and at the same time.
So your server need to handle that much traffic, otherwise it will be trouble for you.
Now, at the time, your registration portal and reserve portal doesn't have that much traffic.
Same applies when universities giving out the results, your citizen portal and examination portal doesn't
have that much topic, just the result portal is having huge traffic because all the students are taking
the results online on your portal.
So what happens at a time one or four or five components are having huge topic and another 20 50 components
doesn't have that much topic, but still you need to scale up all the components.
Why?
Because you have all the components within the same spring board application.
You don't have luxury to just kill one particular component and not others.
Say you have 20 components in your monolithic application, but just one component is having you topic,
then us getting the complete application.
So other 19 components, you don't require much competition, but still you are scaling up your application.
And that's the drawback with monolithic application.
So this is the monolithic application and these are the drawbacks with the monolithic application.
Now, in the next lecture, we will see what is microcircuits and how it is resolving these drawbacks
of the monolithic application.
So that's all for now, will proceed further in the next lecture.
Thank you very much.