Hello and welcome back.
So now our address, micro service is ready, so let's run the address micro surveys and test it out.
So here is our main class.
Let's run it as a springboard application.
So this will take some time and it will get started on board eight zero eight two.
Yes, it got started.
Now let's turn to Posman and here we will create the new address.
So this is a way to address Sless create.
And in the body will pass in the format of Jizan.
St..
See any street?
City.
Say, Mumbai.
Now, let's say this post-paid.
See, the address has been created with it equal to three, we can verify in our address table as well,
it got created.
Now let's try this by Idy.
So address get by ID and I'd call to three.
ID this Gadsby.
We got the response, so these are the address, ladies, whether it equal to three, so now I would
address my groceries is ready now in the upcoming lectures, we will see Student Micro Microcircuits.
So that's all for now.
Will proceed further in the next lecture.
Thank you very much.