Hello and welcome back.
In this lecture, we'll create the address, micro surveys out of this university monolithic application,
and that will be a springboard application.
So let's go for it.
Just click on the file new and spin starter project.
So here you are, the name is Address Service.
So this is our address microcircuits and group is coming to us, cloud whatever you want to give artifact
his address service, this copson address service and this is the picture, click on the next.
And here will select the dependencies.
Bicycle drivers, spring and spring.
This is because our address microcircuits will have the recipes and it will connect to MySQL database
using the spring data G.P.A..
This is the Springwood version I'm using because this is the latest.
When I'm recording this lecture, just click on the next and finish.
It may take a few seconds or a minute to download the dependencies now let let's first configure our
application dot properties so from our monolithic application, let's copy the database properties.
So this will be used by sprint data --.
Now for each Migros service, we will provide a name to that particular microcircuits and that will
be unique across all of our micro services.
So here we will use spring dot application.
Not name and will give it as address service.
Now we are going to run a couple of micro services in our local Muzzin and also we are going to run
the sprinklered cloud projects as well.
So we will run this address.
Microsoft is on board eight zero eight two in our local machine so that we will do using the server
DOT board and provide a value is Ejiro data.
So these are the Maseko database properties.
This is the Microsoft Office name and this is board on which this Microsoft Office will run in our local
machine.
Now, let's create a couple of packages inside the Assad regime in.
So let's first start with controller.
So-called dart in was thought controller and let me copy this part, because we will create a couple
of models as well and the next is service.
Another one is entity that will be having over, and it is for the spring data, Gibeah and.
We will be having one more package for the repository for spring data repositories.
Now we will be having two packages for request and response model classes for our address microcircuits.
So these packages as up now are blank.
Now let's go to our main class that is addressed service application.
And we will copy from our monolithic application this complete thing for the configuration components
can and and enable repositories because we have the same kind of structure for the packages controller
and service inside the components, skin and scandal.
And it is inside this package and enable the repositories that we have inside this particular package.
So here is the structure of our address service is ready.
So that's all for now, will proceed further in the next lecture.
Thank you very much.