Hello and welcome back.
Let's proceed further with our address microcircuits, so from our monolithic application, let's copy
the glass that is addressed, not Java.
And let's inside our address microcircuits.
We don't need to put those two into the glass inside the address my groceries, because this and the
glass will go to Student Microcircuits and that we will see in the upcoming lectures.
Now, let Scoppetta address repository from here and put inside this package OPOWER.
Address my groceries.
Now let's create the.
One model calls for the request to create the address to create address request.
So here we will put the couple of attributes like Private String St..
And city.
So this is all required to create the address.
Let's go getters and setters for these two fields.
Now, let's have one response class to return the address details, and that is a response.
That will be having the same set of attributes.
And one more that is address ID.
Let's get us insiders for this as well.
And we will be having one constructor for this.
To convert the object of a dress into the glass to this model glass that is a dress response, not Jawa,
let's import the address and here will do address I'd call to address dard gaited.
And.
This large, critical to address, does not get straight.
This Darte CD.
Address DOT gets get.
This is to give the response back to the consumer from over entity class, we cannot return this entity
class, right?
So we need the model class and this is what it is converting.
Now, let's move ahead and let's go to the remote controller.
See a dress controller.
Let's market with raised controller.
At the request mapping.
See Sless address, less Epper or let's say Sless AIPA, less address.
Let's import risk, so here we will develop the risk types for the address microcircuits so that we
will see in the next lecture.
Now let's create a service.
Let's market with a service in addition.
So now our address microcircuits is almost ready, we just need to have restabilize inside our address
controller and that we will see in the next lecture.
So that's all for now, will proceed further in the next lecture.
Thank you very much.