Hello and welcome back.
In this lecture, we will address topics in our address microcircuits.
So this is the address Canterlot and here we will add to this DP's one is to create the address and
another one is to get the address by idee.
So this is a post matter and this is gatepost.
For the time being, I have added this to appears in the air traffic controller and here we have a service.
Ordover So whatever it is we want to create that we will get inside this object top model class.
That is basically a very crisp payload in the form of Jason and this model.
Plus we have created in the previous lecture and that's what we are passing to our service layer.
Now here we will create the address using the address repository.
So let's create the new object of address.
And let's assign the values that are coming in this model class in the format of Jason.
So we will set the straight.
GetSet.
It restored said City.
Gets it now here we will use the address repository and using this, we will save the address.
Now, let's return the.
Response, so that is the object of this model class, we have already seen a direct response past object
of address and class, and we have this contractor who is converting from entity class to this response
model class.
So this is to create the address.
Now let's take the another one that is getting the address by I.D. We are getting the idea of the address
in the part variable, and that's what we are passing to Overservice Layer.
Here we have one logger using the logging factory.
Now what we will do, we will use this address repository and we will find the address by ID.
So fine by it.
But the idea that is coming in the request, get it.
And here we are getting the object of the address.
And like this, we will return.
Using the model class that is a stress response, Nardella past the object of entity class that is addressed,
not Java.
So these are two APIs, one to create the address and another one is to get the address.
So that's all for now will proceed further in the next lecture.
Thank you very much.