Hello and welcome back for the upcoming lectures.
We will focus on the sprinklered conflicts are now before we jump to implementation, let's first understand
what these conflicts are about and why we need it.
Now, another example of how to micro services, student and address and for each micro service, the
application properties file and inside that we have a bunch of properties like database properties,
Judicature, where you are, Zipkin server you all and many more properties write.
Now we have different environments like do give and plot, and obviously for each environment, these
properties will have different values, like we have a database for they'll be how you database and
database.
Right.
So obviously they will be having different credentials, username and password.
So this will be applicable for other properties as well.
So how do you manage this environment specific properties for micro services, so that's the solution.
And another thing is that what if we had a change in value for that particular property?
So, for example, we are changing the password database now.
We know that our application, the properties file is inside of packaging meet jar or what?
So you need to redeploy the application.
You just have a change in your application or properties file.
You don't have change in your code.
But still you need to deploy the Microsoft Office.
So the question is how to handle these kind of scenarios.
So what we can do is we can store the environment specific properties in Gaete or Esswein and then we
use git.
It can be Gottleib or get up.
And in this course as well, we are going to use git.
So we will put the properties for our micro services in get now.
We cannot directly refer to it from our micro services because in future, if we are changing the target,
you are right, then it will be a problem for us.
Then we need to change in our micro services and that's a big task.
So here comes config server.
So basically config server is a separate Springwood application.
So what it will do, it will read the properties from the git and from conflicts over our micro services,
will read the properties.
So this is the complete flaw, our properties with storing the git.
From there it will read by config server and then micro services will read from the config server.
So here our config server will register itself with the Eureka server and our micro services can refer
to convict server by service name or you can say service idee.
So in future it can fix server.
You are at least getting ginola then we don't need to worry about it.
Why?
Because we have unica server and other micro services are using the service name of our config server.
Now we have different environments like Dellacqua and brought in context of conflicts are what we call
it as profile, like they profile your profile and broad profile.
So this is what we are going to do, we will store the environment specific properties in it and from
it it will be read by config server and our micro services will read from the config server.
So this is not config server and that's what we are going to implement in the upcoming lecture's.
So using the config server, we can centralize our properties at one place in Guiteau lesbian, right?
We are starting the properties in getable.
So in puter, if you have a chain, you just need to change.
Inderjit report.
That's it.
So this is the use of conflict server and that's what we are going to implement in the upcoming lecture's.
So that's all for now.
Will proceed further in the next lecture.
Thank you very much.