Hello and welcome back.
In this lecture, we will store the micro service properties energy triple.
Now it can be GitHub Gottleib or it can be a local repository as well.
So for simplicity, we will go with the local guide.
So first thing is you need to download and install it in your local machine.
So just search the Google that did download.
This is the official website, Objet.
And according to your operating system, download it and install in your local machine.
Now, after that, go to the directory, whatever it is, OK, in your local mazing, create the new
folder.
So I'm giving the name is Local Rebel.
Whatever you want to.
You give it a name.
Open that folder.
Now, inside this folder, we need to give the properties file for what micro services now lets them
do this.
So for example, we want to store address service properties in the.
So let me open the application properties file.
So these properties we want to store in the local market and we want to use the conflicts that in our
address Microsoft Office, you can do all these things for your other micro services as well here.
Just for an example, I am taking the address service, but this is applicable to all the micro services.
So let's copy these properties file.
And put over here now we need to give this properties file name as our microcircuits name.
So in our example address service is the application name or against the service name.
So let's rename this.
That's all we need to do here.
We are not specifying any environment or you can say profile.
Right.
So it will be a default profile.
So first we are going with the default profile and then we will see different profiles like Dale Kuai
abroad so that we will see in the upcoming Lichter's.
For now we are going with the default profile.
Now we have this application that properties file over here, let me open it, and we need to remove
this one.
We don't require service anymore here.
That's all.
Let me close it now for a disservice.
We don't need these properties, OK?
So apart from application and name, let's remove all the properties.
That's it.
We don't require any other property, just our service name.
We want to have inside this and this file also will remain, but that we will see in the upcoming lectures.
For now, we just have removed the properties.
We just required application anymore here.
Now, this file we added over here.
Right.
But still, it's not committed to a local.
So just open the gate over here.
Now, hit the commanders.
Get in it.
Now, let's add the file that we added, Surjeet, and then space dot.
Now let's commit this one Sloggett comit then our message.
The first commit.
Let's check the status.
Yes, we are on the masterbrand and we have already committed this one fight.
That is a service, not properties.
Now, just copy this, but let's verify.
Go to the browser and go.
See, this is our local guide.
Triple open these properties.
These are the properties we have inside this particular pile.
And this is our guide.
And this is what we are going to use for our config server and from config server.
Our address MICRA service will read these properties.
So as of now, the profile is default.
So this is all we need to do for our local people and restore trust, restored property is vital in
our local people.
Now in the next lecture will create the conflicts are over.
So that's all for now.
Will proceed further in the next lecture.
Thank you very much.