Hello and welcome back.
So now we are all set with our conflicts server over, and in this lecture we will make the changes
in our adversaries so that it can lead to properties using conflicts over whatever properties we have
in our local guide.
These are the properties, right, to sell the properties.
We have a database bought and other things.
So this we are going to read in our address service using that config server.
So there are a couple of dependencies we need to add.
And the first is sprinklered config client and the second is sprinklered starter bootstrap.
So these are the two dependencies.
We need to add in each of the micro services here.
We are taking that service as an example.
So I'm just adding into the service.
But make sure you are adding all these things in your all micro services.
So these two dependencies we are adding into the bombed out XML better service.
Now let's open the application properties for our address service.
Now here we need to define Capullo properties so that it can fetch the properties using config server.
Now we know that we are using the Utica in our country server application.
So basically config server has registered with the Eureka server.
So we need to define in the service that look for the config Savarin Eureka.
That is our service discovery so that we need to do using the spring cloud dart config.
That discovery enabled equal to true.
So this is done property, we need to set that look for the convicts that were using the service discovery
in our case, Eureka.
Now, the next thing we need to do is we need to provide the application name of other conflicts are
over so that we need to do using the spring cloud.
Config tarde, discovery service ID, so that is config server.
This is what you provided as application name in your config server.
So this is the application, not properties for our config server.
So whatever you pointed or here is something that you need to provide us service ID or you can say service
name or application name, whatever.
Now using these properties, we are looking into the Eureka server and finding the configuration and
address service will use this config server to pass the required properties.
Now, say you are not using UDCA in your config server, then you need to provide that you are all of
your config server.
So for that, you need to provide property, asprin, cloud, config, dard.
You are right and provide you are all of your config server.
So localhost colonnaded edit because our config server is running in our local machine on board eight
eight eight eight.
So if you are using the service discovery in your config server, like we use the Utica, then you need
to set these two properties and if you are not using Eureka in your conflicts work, then directly you
need to provide the are of your config server.
So here we are using the Utica in the conflict.
So this property I'm just commenting out for your reference, if you want to go by this way and don't
want to use the Utica in config server, then you need to set this property.
So this is for your reference.
Now we want to read these properties from our local get people using the convicts are the last thing
we need to do for that is we need to rename this application that properties as bootstrap properties.
If you are not renaming this, then it will not work.
So to work with convicts are what you need to rename your application that properties as bootstrap properties.
And you need to define these two properties that you are enabling service discovery for config server
and you are looking for the conflict server using this service idea.
Or you can say service name or you can say application name.
So now we are all set with our config server and address microcircuits.
So let's test it out quickly.
So first we will start with Unica server as usual, and then we will start the conflict server and we
don't need a big win for now.
Live it.
Let's talk directly.
Address service.
We might see some errors or exception for the Zipkin or maybe I get it, but we will ignore those for
now.
For the time being, we are directly going to to address service.
Wait for it, yeah, see, it is establishing the database connection that means it is reading these
properties, otherwise we should have seen the errors in this start up, only we haven't got anything.
See, it started on the board, a zero eight three.
And here we haven't provided the board.
And here it's reading Ejiro entry.
So let's go to Posman.
And here.
Let's directly hit the address service, localhost it 083 Slash Epper.
Let's address let's get Bidi, I'd call to one.
We got the success response.
This is only possible if our service is reading these properties, whatever we have in our report.
Local people basically using the conflicts are what if our service is not adding those properties using
the conflict server, then this response is not possible.
So this is how you can use conflict server in your micro services.
And this is the two properties that you need to set in each of your micro services.
And these two dependencies you need to add one sprinklered conflict line.
And the second is bring cloud startup bootstrap.
So this is how you can use sprinklered config server in your micro services, so that's all for now.
We'll see you in the next lecture.
Thank you very much.