Hello and welcome back here.
Our address microcircuits is reading the properties using config Sarovar and the profile we said is
the.
And these are the properties it is reading using the config Sarwan.
Now, say, for example, for a property, we are changing its value.
For example, this property right address noticed we are changing its value from testing to see, for
example, change the value.
This is just one example.
OK, so we have a change in the property value for the property.
Now, let's see if we can fix that.
What is getting the updated value or not?
So let's jump to Posman and let's see the conflicts are over for our address.
Micro service properties do click on the same you to the profile to scroll down see address noticed.
It is changing the value.
That means our conflicts are what is reading the updated value.
So we are good with our config server because it is getting the updated value.
Now how about our address microcircuits?
So let's take it out that as well.
So this is the last test.
This is what reading the property right.
Address noticed.
So click on this n c still it is getting the old value that is testing here.
We have changed its value from testing to change the value of a conflict.
So nobody's getting the updated value.
But still our micro Sarbaz is reading the old value.
It's not getting the updated value.
Why?
The reason is that when you start to microsatellites right, it will read the properties on start up
using the config server.
So after your MicroStrategy starts and you have a change in the property, even your config server is
getting the updated value.
Your MICRA service will not get the updated value because it has read the properties on the start up
using the config server and after that you made a change for the property so it will not get updated
value for your property.
And this is what happening over here.
So if you want that, your address, Microsoft read the latest value, whatever, we change it for the
property, then what do you need to do?
You need to restart your address.
Microsoft Office.
So let me stop the address.
Microsoft Office, wait for a few seconds.
Just ignore the Zipkin and Gateway errors or hear because I'm directly running the address.
Microsoft Office.
Yes.
Now, Wittstock, let me start again.
Pressed Microsoft Office.
So here we are just running the server configure and address Microsoft Office.
Now, let's try this again and see if it is reading the updated value or not.
See, now it's giving us the change of value, so what we need to do, we need to restart our micro
service if we have a change in property value.
But this is not a good thing, right?
We have just one property value changed and we need to restart our micro services, even our conflicts.
Server is reading the updated value.
Still, we need to restart our Microsoft Office.
So what to do in this case?
That's what we are going to see in the next lecture, that how to read the updated value in your micro
servers without restarting your Microsoft office so that we will see in the next lecture.
So that's all for now.
We'll see you in the next lecture.
Thank you very much.