Hello and welcome back.
For the upcoming lectures.
We will be focusing on the tolerance and circuit breaker for our micro services and for that we are
going to use resilience for the micro services.
But before that, you need to understand a few concepts.
Now, let's first see the problem scenario.
Let's see what are the failures that can be possible with our micro services, so in our example, we
know that student service is calling the address service.
Now, it may be possible that a drug service itself is down.
The second thing is that a drug service is having high failure rate.
There can be any reasons for a drug service to have high failure rate.
It may be possible that a drug service has some issue while connecting to a database or any other reason.
And because of that, it's a high failure rate.
Now, this kind of illness can be possible to any of your micro services.
So now the question is how to deal with this kind of.
So that's what we are going to cover in the upcoming elections and we are going to use resilience for
hour micro services to handle this kind of failures.
So that's all for now will proceed further in the next lecture.
Thank you very much.