Hello and welcome back.
In this lecture, we will see what is for tolerance and why we need it.
So in our example, student service is calling the address service and say, for example, address service
is having some issue.
And because of that, it's observing more failures.
Now, because of this, what will happen, our student service will also observe more failures.
Now, say, for example, result service is calling the student service.
So the same will apply to result service as well.
It will also observe more failures.
And same for examination service as well, because examination service is calling the result service.
So here we just have issue or fault in our address service, but it is getting prosecuted to our other
Migros services.
Now, here we just have four micro services.
But when you are working in the real time application, right, you might be having hundreds of or thousands
of micro services.
Now, just imagine that you are one micro service is having some issue.
And because of that, either 100 or 200 micro service is getting impacted.
So that should not happen.
Right.
So here comes the fault tolerance.
So here we know that our address, micro surveys is having some issues.
Now we will try that the issues should not get cascaded to other micro services.
So we will try that our other micro services will have minimal impact.
So this is for tolerance and why we need it, so that's all for now, will proceed further in the next
lecture.
Thank you very much.