Hello and welcome back.
In this lecture, we will see what is circuit breaker now for this lecture only.
Forget about the spring board, spring cloud and micro services, because in this lecture we will understand
what is circuit breaker by taking the real world example.
So here we have home and in our home, we have electronic items such as fridge, TV, as the washing
machine and many more.
Right.
And this is the electricity source here.
We have one electrical switch.
If this suite is closer to that means electricity is flowing into our home.
If this switches open, that means electricity is not flowing in our home.
So, for example, as of now, this which is closed.
So electricity is flowing in our home.
Now, see, we have some issue in our home, it may be higher voltage or any other reason, and because
of that, our fridge got damaged.
And if this continues, then it may be possible that other electronics items may get damaged.
So we don't want to have that right.
So nowadays, in most of the homes, we have an electrical switch which will identify if there is an
issue in our home, it will automatically make this switch as open.
So if the suite is open, that means electricity will not flow in over a home.
So that's total power cut in our home.
Nothing will work be to blight fan or any other electronic item.
By making the switch open, we are saving other electronic items in our home.
Our fridge got damaged, but at least we sell with other electronic items by getting damaged.
So this is a circuit breaker.
This electricity is blowing when the switch is closer and we brought this circuit by making this switch
as open.
Now, you may call the electrician, the guy will come and he will examine the home, if everything
is fine, then he will make the switch as closely.
So he switches closer.
Then again, electricity will flow into your home.
So this is a circuit breaker in context of electrical switch, we broke the circuit with the help of
this electrical switch.
Now in the next lecture, we will see the circuit breaker in context of our micro services.
So that's all for now, will proceed further in the next lecture.
Thank you very much.