Hello and welcome back.
In this lecture, we will see what are the different states of a circuit breaker, Ken, how so?
Now you know that we have a switch and in this lecture we will see what are the different states the
can have.
So here there are three different states of a switch or you can see a circuit breaker can help.
The first is Clouzot.
So the suite is closed and that means all calls are allowed.
So in our example, student service is calling address service and Ipswitch is closed.
That means all calls from student service to address service are allowed.
The second state is open, if the suite is open, that means no calls allowed.
So basically no calls from room service to address service are allowed.
So this is the open state for work switch.
Now, the third state our suite can have is half open or you can zip partially open.
So basically, it's not blocking all the calls and also it is not allowing all the calls, but it will
just allow some few number of calls to go from student to address service.
For example, our student service is calling the address service and the call rate is 100 per second.
So if the switches happen, then it will just allow 10 or 20 calls to go out of hundred this 10 or 20
we can configure.
It's up to us that how many calls we want to allow in the half open state to go from student to address
service.
So here, if the state is half open, that means it's not allowing all the calls and as well it is not
blocking all the 100 calls, but it's partially allowing a few calls to go from student to address service.
And that's the half open state for the circuit breaker or switch, whatever you say.
Now, these three states is in our hand, how we want to configure, we just need to set up a few residents
for the properties and we can configure these three different states that when we want to make the switch
closer, when we want to make the switch is open and when we want to make the switch as half open,
it's completely up to us.
And also how many calls we want to allow to go in the open.
One state that is basically partially allowing the calls, all things we can configure using the resilience
for the properties.
Now, what are those properties?
That's what we are going to see in the next lecture, so that's all for now.
We'll see you in the next lecture.
Thank you very much.