Hello and welcome back.
In this lecture, we will see the different properties that we are going to use to configure our circuit
breaker, or you can see our sweet.
So the very first, an important one is sliding window size.
So for this property, we need to provide the numeric value that how many calls we want to consider
to make the decision that we want to make the suite from closer to open.
So, for example, we want to consider last hundred calls or say 200 calls so that we need to define
using this property.
That is a sliding window size.
Let's take an example.
Say student service is calling the address service and the rate is a thousand calls per minute.
Now, if we said the sliding window size is 100, then it will take the last hundred calls.
So that's nine hundred one two one thousand.
Now, in a few seconds, one hundred more calls made from student to address service.
So total calls are eleven hundred and of a sliding window sizes.
So now it will take the one thousand one to eleven hundred.
So whatever we provide for this property that will be large number of calls will be considered.
So that's the sliding window size that we need to define.
So this is very important property and here we need to give numeric value.
Now we know we have three states, four of us, which closed the open and half open.
Now we need to provide that how much percentage of fault we want to tolerate.
And if the failure rate is greater than the threshold, then make the sweet states open so that we need
to define using the failure rate threshold.
So this is the percentage we need to provide this property in terms of percentage.
See federal threshold equal to 50 percent and I was sliding windows equal 200 and now out of last 100
calls say, for example, 60 calls are feeling.
So our failure rate is 60 percent, which is greater than 50 percent, whatever we said for this particular
property.
So now here, sweet state will become from closer to open.
So this is the property we need to set in terms of percentage.
Now the sweet state is open, but he cannot be in the open state for a long period of time, so we need
to define that how many seconds we want to be in the open state.
So for that, we have this property, we do this on in open state, and we can provide second set,
for example, 30 seconds.
We want to be in the open state this period of time.
We are giving to address service so that it can resolve its issues, whatever it is having.
For this period of time, the switch is open, so no calls from student to address service are allowed.
So we are not bombarding on the address service from the student service and we are giving some time
to address service to recover from the issue, whatever it is having.
As I said, we cannot be in the open state for a long period of time and we need to go into a half open
state from the open sea.
We cannot directly go to closing the state from the open, from the open state.
We can go to half open state only.
And after this time expires, do we want to automatically join the sweet state from open to half open.
If yes, then we need to set don't believe property that is automatic transition from open to half open
state.
So if this property is true, then once this time expires, the switch will be gone from open to half
open and that will become automatically because we are setting this property as true.
Now, in hobgoblins, did we know that we can allow some number of calls to go from student to address
service?
So, for example, we want to allow five calls to go from student to either service in half or one state.
So this is the property we need to set.
But we did a number of calls in one state, for example, right now in half open state.
Again, it will take for the failure rate on this number of calls.
And if the failure rate is still greater than the threshold, whatever we said, then again, the switch
will be gone from half open to open.
If the failure rate is less than the threshold, what would be said then?
The switch will become from Harpe.
Open to.
Closer to.
So these are the important properties, let's recap all the things very quickly.
The first is sliding window size, how many last calls we want to consider.
And based on that, we want to take that decision now how much percentage of fault we want to tolerate.
If the failure rate based on this sliding window size is greater than the threshold, then make the
switch as open.
Now, how much do this and we want to wait in the open state, for example, 30 second, up to 30 second.
Do we want to automatically switch to half open just then?
Here is the property now.
How many calls we want to allow in open state, for example, right now, based on these five calls,
again, it will take the failure rate.
If the failure rate is still greater than the threshold, that means still there is some issue in that
address service.
Go to the open state for the switch.
Now, if the failure rate is less than the threshold, that means extra service has resolved any issue.
So make the switch as closely.
So these are the important properties, sliding window size, failure rate threshold.
They do this on in open state, automatic transmission from open to half of one state and the number
of calls in half or one state.
So these are the properties we need to put in our student service because student service is calling
the A service.
These properties are very important to configure to a circuit breaker, and based on these properties,
only of a suite will behave.
So make sure you are getting all the things that what are the properties we need to set for our configuration
part?
So these are the different properties that we are going to use for our circuit breaker, so that's all
for now.
We'll see you in the next lecture.
Thank you very much.