Hello and welcome back for the upcoming lectures.
We are going to implement circuit breaker using Resilience 4G.
So let's start by adding the dependencies in the bombed out XML for a student service.
So the very first dependency we need to add is resilience for this spring.
Bhuto and this is the latest version when I'm recording this lecture.
Whatever is latest version, when you are watching this, you can go for it now.
Internally, Resilience for days using Spring LP.
So we need to add your dependency as well and that is a springboard starter LP.
Now to take the current state of the suite, we are going to use the actuator.
So this is the dependency we need to add for actuator.
That is a springboard starter actuator.
So make sure you are adding these three dependencies in the bombed out XML for your student service.
Now, let's make a slight change in our student service, so you remember this matter.
Earlier, we used to make the call to address service, but that was using that Web client.
But now we are using the front line.
So let's remove this word here.
And this piece of code to make the call to address service will put over here like this.
Address response.
And.
Return the address response.
And we will call this matter from here.
Same thing we will do over here.
So now we have this method to make the call to address service, and here we need to address it.
Now we are good.
So on this matter, we will apply the circuit breaker, because inside this matter only we are making
the call to address service.
So we are going to implement the circuit breaker on this particular matter.
So that we will see in the upcoming lectures.
So that's all for now will proceed further in the next lecture.
Thank you very much.