Hello and welcome back in one of the previous lectures we have seen, what are the properties we need
to configure for our circuit breaker?
Now, in this lecture, we will set those properties to configure our circuit breaker using resilience
energy.
So just open the application properties of the student service and here we will set those properties.
So let's start by adding those properties.
So resilience for the.
Not a circuit breaker and instances now we need to give the instanced name, you can give any let me
give a meaningful say address service.
Now, the first thing we need to set is sliding window size.
How many last calls we want to consider?
And based on that, we want to make that decision that suites would be either open closing or help open.
So the sliding window size.
For example, we want to consider last 10 calls.
Now let's let other properties.
So let me copy this.
But this is the other instance.
Name the next is threshold.
So if the failure rate is greater than or equal to the threshold, then make the switch as open.
So here.
Filaret also, for example, 50 percent, this is in the percentage.
OK, so if failure rate is greater than or equal to 50 percent, make the switch as open.
Now, the next is once the switch is open, how many seconds we want to wait in the open state.
Right.
So wait duration in open state.
So here we need to go in milliseconds.
For example, we want to wait for 30 seconds in the open state, so we need to give thirty thousand
milliseconds.
So this time we are making that the switch should be open.
So our address service will get this time to recover from that issue.
Whatever it is having now after this duration expires, right after the 30 seconds we want to make,
the switch has happened automatically, right.
So automatic transmission from open to half open, equal to two.
So after the 30 seconds in the open state, it will automatically make the swing state as half open
now in the half open state, we can allow some calls to go right.
So that is permitted number of calls.
So, for example, we want to allow five calls in the hopper open state.
So these are the properties we need to set for the resilience for the circuit breaker.
Now, to take the current state of the switch, we can use actuator and we have already added the dependancy
in the bombed out XML for actuator so far that we need to configure a few properties.
So let's see that part as well.
So here.
Allow health indicators to feel equal to true and another property we need to set is.
Register health indicator equal to two.
So these are the two properties for actuator to configure along with the resilience for them.
Now there are a couple of properties we need to set for actuator itself.
Like, we need to enable the less health endpoint so that we need to start using the management not.
Held dart circuit breaker enabled a call to Drew.
And the next is management dot.
And point start.
Web expos include a call to.
The next is management.
Thought and point, here is the typo, let me correct it out, so management, so Opteron point held.
Lots of details equal to always, so these are the three properties we need to set for the actuator
and these two properties to work with the resilience for the circuit breaker along with the actuator
and these properties we have set for circuit breaker now to check the current state of the switch.
There are a couple of things we need to look for in the actuator.
So here we have three states, whatever suite.
Right?
So the first is closer to the second is open.
And the authorities have opened.
Now, Actuator will not use these terms, too, so the Swedes did so for closure, it will soirées up
for open, it will say is down and for half open it will say is unknown.
So whenever we are using the actuator to take the current state of the switch, it will not use these
terms like close, low, open or how open it will use up for the state.
It will use down for the open state and for half open.
It will use as unknown.
So make sure you remember these three things while taking the current state of the suite using actuator
now using this instance name.
Let's go to school and service.
And here inside this matter, we are making the call to address service.
Right.
So here we will mark this as a circuit breaker.
And in the name, we need to provide the instance name, so in our example, we have a dress service.
This is the instance name, whatever you provided or hear the same, you need to provide using this
as a circuit breaker.
In addition, and here using the front line, we are making the call to address service about this matter.
We need to use the circuit breaker annotation and provide the instance name.
So what we need here is let's recap the things we said, the resilience for the properties, for the
circuit breaker, we said the properties for actuator to display the current state of the sweet.
And these are the states it will store in the actuator, up, down in unknown.
Now, using this instance name, we market over matter with the circuit breaker and.
So that's all we did in this lecture.
Now, the further configuration we will see in the next lecture.
So that's all for now.
We'll see you in the next lecture.
Thank you very much.