Hello and welcome back.
In the previous lecture, we noted this matter using the annotation as a circuit breaker and we provided
the instance Naem.
Now here we are making the RESCALE to address service now.
For example, our address service is getting some error or Sipson, be it for four or five hundred internal
server error.
OK, so we are not getting the proper response from address service.
So in that case, we need to provide the fallback method and instead the fallback method will return
the dummy response.
So here we need to provide another attribute that is Folbigg matter and we need to provide the name
of Folbigg method.
So let's provide like this.
Folbigg and get addressed by Idy You can give any name, you can just give meaningfully.
So we need to create this method that is basically our fallback method.
Now, by creating the Folbigg method, you need to remember one thing that it must have the same method
signature as your method on which you have a circuit breaker a.D.A.
So in our case, this is the method get addressed by Idy.
Let me copy all the things from here and put me over here.
This is the method name.
Now we are good and here we need to return the dummy response, so, for example, we are returning
new object of interest response.
You can return anything.
OK, this is Dommy response.
Why?
Because we are not getting the proper response from the service.
So it will go to our fallback method and will return the dummy response, whatever we want to return.
Another example, we are just returning the new object of interest response and it must have the same
method signature as your method on which you have a circuit breaker annotation.
Now, one more parameter you can set in the method and that is optional and that is provable.
Like this, so this will give you the exception if you want to log so that we will see in the upcoming
lectures.
OK, but this is a personal one.
This is much because it shouldn't matter what method signature for this matter on which we have a circuit
breaker annotation.
And here we provided the fallback method.
And this is our fallback method.
Now say the speed is closer.
So here it will try to call the address service using the faint light and say, for example, it is
returning, though, find it internal server error.
So it will come forward for dark matter and it will return the dummy response.
It will not fail, though, student service.
Instead of that, it will return the dummy response from the fallback method.
Whatever we provided no set.
For example, switch is open, so no calls are allowed from student to address service.
So this matter will not get executed because we are not allowed to make the calls to address service.
So this piece of code, basically whatever we have in this matter will not get executed.
Instead of that, it will directly come to our fallback method and will return the dummy response.
The same applies.
What happens data is, well, we are allowing five calls in the open state.
And so, for example, Edra Service is giving some exception.
So it will come to our fallback and will return the dummy response.
So the bottom line is, whatever the state the suite is having, it will always come to our fallback
method.
If a service is giving some error, exception doesn't matter.
Whatever state you have for your switch.
If a service is having some issue, it will come to your fallback method and it will return the dummy
response.
So that's the use of fallback method.
The fallback method must need to have the same method signature as like your method on which you have
a circuit breaker and descent and you can use this optional one trouble to lock the exception.
So this is the use of Fulbeck method.
So that's all for now will proceed further in the next lecture.
Thank you very much.