Hello and welcome back.
Now we are all set with Slewed, so let's test it out.
So first we will start the Eureka server, then we will start the API gateway after that, what Migros
Services student and address.
So Disservices API Gateway will take some time.
Let me maximize the console, because here we are going to see the president sponsored for our Advanced
Micro Services.
Give these services some time to up and configure the EPA gateway, this is started a retro service.
Let me clear the logs now in the EPA gateway.
Let me clear the logs and for our student service as well.
Let me clear the logs now give this service is a minute to configure because we know, right sometimes
with a gateway, we are getting four or four.
So let's jump to Postman and wait for a minute or hear.
Now, let's hit this to get this, somebody just click on the same.
We got the response, but we are interested into the logs, so first we will start from the EPA gateway,
so let them do be a gateway.
See, these are the logs you see.
And if you go outside, this is for pre filter and post filter.
But here we are interested in this one.
This is the service name.
Whatever we have given in the application, that is fine.
This is the tree side and this is the spotted.
So see this idea, this Arsène and same for this one, is it?
But we are interested into this one.
So let me copy this.
This is theme, and that is obvious right now.
Let's jump to student service, search for it.
So we got it.
So we have to log statements.
The first is inside the student body and then we are calling the address that is using the faint line
that we have inside the Common Service.
Right.
We have already seen.
So this is C C that it is same as we have in our gateway.
But Sponer, it is different.
But these two logs are having the same sponte.
So if we look at within the micro surveys, then two logs are belong to one request only where this
is the spidy.
So this is how you can trust within the micro service.
Now let's turn to address Microscopist such for Braeside.
Yeah.
There you go.
This is the Treasury, this is the sponte, and we just have one long statement in a dress service,
but see, the Treasury is saying this is the application name, whatever be given in the application
that properties and this is those PINETTI.
Now, if we have any other long statement within the same request, obviously it will have the same
span idee.
Now, we started off with that idea.
So basically we traced that request across all the micro services and epigraphy because that this idea
will remain missing.
And if you want to trace down the request within the micro service, go with this PINETTI like this
this log statements, whatever you have, OK?
It doesn't matter.
100, 200 search with sponte and all belongs to one request only so you can easily trace down the request
within the service.
Same applies for what?
API Gateway application as well.
So this is the formal application name, then your Tayside and Spidey.
So now we are seeing all these things in the logs that we trace down the request across the micro devices
and Gateway and using the Spinetta with trace down within the Microsoft Office.
That's fine.
But how about the UI?
What if we can have UI for this?
We just provide the press ID and it will provide us complete floor that from back to where the request
is going.
So for example, from Gateway to Service and from there to address service so that if we want to see
in the UI, then we need to use Zipkin.
And for that Zipkin is providing Zipkin server and that's what we are going to implement in the upcoming
lecture's.
So that's all for now.
We'll see you in the next lecture.
Thank you very much.