Hello and welcome back.
So now we are all set with Sloup and Zipkin, so let's test it out.
So here all things are running Unica, Savar, a big gateway, and our micro services that are student
and address services.
And Zipkin is running on the bottom line for in our local mussen.
OK, so let's do Posman.
Let's say this Garibay.
So now we got the response.
Let's go to Browsr and here just click on this run query.
See, we got this one request.
OK, so if you click on this run query, it will list down all the request.
So just click on the saw.
See, this is the complete flaw for this particular request that we just now hit.
So the request was coming to get away from there, it's going to in service, and we know that from
room service, we are calling it a service, but that call is not direct.
We are using the EPA gateway to call the address service from a student service so that also you can
see or hear from students service to EPA Gateway and from Gateway.
It's going to address service.
You see, this is the sponsored and this is the matter.
This is the air traffic controller, the Mitani.
Same for one student service.
This is the you are right and you see the student controller method and all the things are to get better.
So this is the complete flaw for this particular request.
Now let's go back and here you see this plus button.
Just click on it.
Select the service name.
Now it is doing all the applications, see, address, service, get the instrument service.
Why?
Because for these three springboard applications, the editor sleuth Zipkin dependancy, and also we
provided the Sipkin Sawat, you are ill.
So now click on the Gateway and you can query Orien.
You get the same result.
OK, now let's turn down the request by Tracery.
So let's jump to ideas and copy this.
You can pick destress from any of the logs because we know.
Right pressingly same across all the micro services along with the API Gateway.
Now just put this president here.
Don't click on the enter.
There you go.
See the same request.
Now we can see.
So whenever you have the tragedy in hand, right, and you want to turn down the request, just go to
the Zipkin settlement, put the Presidio here and he the enter it will show you the complete floor for
this particular request.
So this is how you can trust the request using Sloup and Zipkin, so that's all for now.
We'll see you in the next lecture.
Thank you very much.