Hello and welcome back.
Now you know what is office, right?
And we can handle hundreds of our thousands of Microsoft offices.
Now, if we manage this micro services manually, then it will be a big task.
So don't worry.
Here comes the spring cloud to rescue the developers.
So basically, spring cloud is having the projects that will help the developers to quickly develop
and maintain the micro services.
If you want to check out all the projects provided by the spring cloud, then here is the official Web
site.
Go ahead and check it out in the next lecture.
We will see the spring cloud projects that we are going to cover in this course.
So we'll see you in the next lecture.
Thank you very much.