Hello and welcome back.
Let's have an overview of sprinklered projects that are covered in this course.
So the first is sprinklered upon Fien, so what happens over micro services can communicate with each
other with different methods, like using the ATP Protocol, say, for example, of a student micro
service is calling the receptors up, address microcircuits or any other microcircuits beed examination
result microcircuits.
Another is using the DU or accent mechanism like a project to MQ or Rabbitt MQ.
But generally micro services can talk with each other in a TDP protocol using the rest DPAs.
So we need an easy way to integrate this so that our micro services can communicate with each other
and we.
How is integration?
So that comes to sprinklered upon Fien.
The next is Sprinklered, Cloud, Netflix, Eureka, as I said that we can how thousands of micro services,
right.
And if we were micro services are communicating with each other.
And if we have a change in you all for any of the micro services, then it will be a big problem for
us.
And we need to change that.
You are all in all the micro services, so don't worry.
Here comes the Eureka server, which is service this Korean registry.
So what happens?
Each of our micro surveys will register itself with the Utica and it will be having the unique ID or
name.
So what happens?
Our micro service will communicate with another micro service using the service name.
It will not use the you are allowed another micro service.
So it is very easy.
Say, for example, you are migrating from Amazon cloud to as you now you are not dependent on the you
are because you have UDCA server.
So what happens?
Your micro services will use the service name and with that it will communicate with other micro services
and it is not dependent on that.
You are a micro services.
Just imagine if micro service is using that.
You are to love another micro service and you have change in.
You all say you are migrating from Amazon cloud to your.
Then it will be a big problem for you and it's a big task for you.
The next is spring cloud load balancer, several student micro is calling addressed Microsoft Office.
Now, we can have multiple instances for our Microsoft Office right now.
For example, we have two instance for our address, Microsoft Office.
So we need some kind of load balancing between those instances, whatever requests are coming right.
We need to have some kind of load balancing mechanism.
So here our student micro service is calling the address Microsoft Office.
So here, Student Micro Services client.
So Spring Cloud Load Balancer is providing a way to have blindsight load balancing.
The next is Spring Cloud API, Gateway API Gateway is the entry point for each of the micro services,
whatever requests coming to each of the micro services will first come to Epper Gateway so that we can
perform some common things like authentication.
If you want to put some request headers, response headers or logging, whatever you want to do, whatever
requests are coming to your micro services will first come to your Epper Gateway.
Here you can perform some common operations.
The next is for tolerance, say you're one microscopist is down now, it should not have impact on other
micro services, right?
So there comes the fault tolerance.
In migrant services, pricing is very important.
For example, one request is coming to your student service.
Now, student service internally calls the address service address service, calls to examination service
and examination service, calls to reserve service.
So like this, you can how many calls between your micro services.
So what happens if anything goes wrong and you want to trace it down, then it will be a problem.
So don't worry.
Here comes the --.
So using this --, you can transfer the request where it is going and how your micro services are
communicating.
You are getting the complete flow.
Zipkin is the UI tool to see this complete flow that from where to where your request is going, you
can see that, OK, from student micro surveys to address micro servers and from there it is going to
examination and so on.
So basically, you can trace it down the requests that are coming to your micro services.
Now you have some common set of properties for each of your micro services.
For example, database properties, right, database, username, password, you warrell database,
Nimoy's or schema and other things.
So you have this set of properties for each of the environmental integration brought and so on.
And hundreds of micro services that you have will use these properties.
Now, say, for example, you have change in some credentials.
So why do you need to do is that you need to go in for each of the micro surveys, basically your application
dot properties file and you need to change in each of those files.
So that's a hectic task, right.
So there comes the configuration server.
We can store these common properties at some place, you can help get people as well, whatever you
prefer, from there, each of your micro surveys will read those properties.
So what happens in the future?
If you have a change in property, you just need to change in your target reports, for example, and
all your micro surveys will use that updated property.
Just update at the one place and all your micro services will get the updated property value.
So this is the uses of configuration server.
So this is an overview of sprinklered, projects that are covered in this course that's all for now,
will proceed further in the next lecture.
Thank you very much.