Hello and welcome back.
In this lecture, we will see what is microcircuits, so let's divide this micro and service that means
small service or you can say small springboard application.
Here I am taking the context of Springwood, because this course is all about micro services with Springwood
and sprinklered, but this concept of micro service is applicable for any of the programming language
or you are using any weapon work like start drop visored or any other sport python that promotes the
concept of micro service is seen.
So here is our university monolithic application.
So what we can do is that each of these components we can make as separate spring boot application,
so that will be microcircuits.
So, you know, example, we have six components.
So what will happen?
Student micro surveys address Microsoft Office and same like for faculty Professor Examinees unresolved.
And if any other component is that the same is applicable, each of these components will become separate
spring boot application, and that is called as microcircuits.
So we can say like we have student service at service and so on.
So likewise you can have hundreds of or thousands of micro services divided from the monolithic application.
So over monolithic application will be divided into small, small spring application that is called
as micro service.
Now let's see how this micro service concept is resolving the drawbacks of the monolithic application.
So the first is called complexity.
So what happens now?
We have a small, small springboard applications, right?
So we have small Corbis in the particular Microsoft Office.
So it is very easy to handle for the developer or for the team who is working on that particular Microsoft
Office.
If you have a change in one micro service, you just need to test that particular microcircuits, only
you don't need to test all the micro services so each developer or the team of the developers can focus
on the different different micro services.
Now, let's come to the second drawback of monolithic application, and that is tight coupling of the
components now here in the microcircuits architecture.
What happens?
We have a small, small springboard applications, right, running separately.
So what happens?
Say your student service is down, then your examination and result service will not have any impact.
Those services are still running.
So what happens in monolithic application?
Your complete application is going down while here.
What happens?
Just one micro service is going down, but others are running.
So you can focus on the particular service that is down and you can bring it up.
Till then, either micro services are running and are in function mode.
So here in micro services architecture, you don't have tight coupling between the micro services.
The is scalability.
So it's there, for example, at the decision time you can scale up the student service to handle the
huge traffic.
You don't need to scale other micro services like address, faculty examination or result.
Also on in the same way, when university is taking the examination, you just need to scale up your
examination, micro surveys.
And we know right in the cloud it's very easy to scale up or scale down the services.
Doesn't matter if you are using Amazon cloud, Microsoft major or Portal Cloud Foundry or any other
cloud platform.
In the same way, when university is announcing the results, you can scale down the other micro services
like student examination, and you can scale up the result Microsoft Office to handle the huge traffic
for that particular period.
So here you are not scaling up and scaling down all the Microsoft offices.
What happens in the monolithic?
You need to scale up complete application so all the components.
So here in the case of Microsoft architecture, you are just scaling up and scaling down the particular
micro services.
And by that you are saving the cost because we know that increasing the instances will cost you.
So these are the advantages of the Microsoft Office or the monolithic application.
So that's all for now will proceed further in the next lecture.
Thank you very much.