Hello and welcome back.
In this lecture, we will create the configuration server, so that is basically a springboard application.
So let's go for it.
Let's create a new spring board application.
The name is Config Server.
This is the group that we want to help and artifact is config server.
The package we want is come in, Pybus a click on the next.
And here we need to add the dependencies config server.
So just search for config server and this dependency.
Now our config server application will register itself with Eureka server.
So we also need to add the Eureka client dependency.
So these two dependencies, we need to add in our config server application, click on the next and
finish.
So this might take a few seconds to a minute to download the required dependencies.
Now.
Let's go to the main class of this conflict, the replication, or just wait for a few more seconds.
Yes, now we are good, I think.
Yes.
Open the main class here.
We need to enable.
Config are.
Yeah, this one, so we are seeing that this is not the normal springboard application, but this is
unfixable.
Now, this application will register itself with Yuriko Starbright so we know how to do so.
We will enable.
You declined as well.
So that's all we need to do in our meaningless now lets them do application properties.
And here first, we'll start with Savar DART Board, equal to eight eight eight eight.
So this is the port on which we are going to run our config server in local mussing.
Now, the next is spring dart application.
Dot name.
Let's give a name as Confit Savar.
Now we need to provide a legit repository, right, so for that, we need to set property a spring cloud.
Config.
Savar.
DARD, Gitte.
You are right.
Yes, that's all we need to say.
So for us, this is the report.
You want to select this one and provide this like this.
So make sure you are including file, because this is from our local machine.
So you need to have this one in the starting.
And then the part where you have this application that properties in our example address service, DOT
properties.
Now we need to register with UDCA server.
So we need to provide you all of Eurekas.
Right.
So let's copy from one of the application.
So this is the Eureka server.
Let me copy.
And we will put like this.
So this is all we need to do in the main class, we need to enable the conflicts that over registered
with Utica and we need to provide whatever triple and Utica what you are.
This is the things that we are almost providing in any spring application, be it our micro service,
EPA, Godwill or whatever it is right now, we are all set with our config server.
So first we will start with Eureka Server and then we will start our config server application.
So let's run it as a springboard application.
You some time to end this conflict or application to register whether.
Let's wait for a minute.
Yeah, it got started on eight, eight, eight.
Now let's turn to both men and hear the wall of conflicts over localhost.
Edit, edit now what service we are looking for, for us address service.
So this is the service name now profile is default, so less default.
So we got the response, let's get out what we are getting to this is the report where we help address
the properties.
And these are the properties it is getting from this particular properties that we have in this report.
So if you open this one see three, four, five, six, total six properties we have and here we are
getting six properties.
So this is how you can retrieve what properties inside a particular profile you want to know for your
conflicts in the name of your groceries and sless profile.
For now, we just have the full profile and upcoming lichter's.
We will see how to have different profiles like Del Dewey or whatever it is.
But for now, if you are not provide anything right like address, service or properties, then by default
this profile is default.
So now we are ready with our convict server now in the next lecture, we will prepare our address service
so that it can use config server and fetch the required properties from here that we provided in the
triple, but not directly using the config server.
So that's all we are going to do in the next lecture.
So that's all for now.
We'll see in the next lecture.
Thank you very much.