Hello and welcome back here.
Our address service is reading the properties using config server, but the profile is default.
So what if we want to read the profile specific properties in our address service?
So, for example, the profile or you can go with our broad profile.
So that's what we are going to do in this lecture.
So let's turn to our local get people and let's copy this one.
Now, let's provide this name so to your microcircuits name, hyphen your profile.
Say, for example, the profile for our address microcircuits.
So this is the name of all my groceries.
I found your profile in our example.
They let me open it.
Notepad plus plus.
Now these two are having the same set of properties.
So to distinguish and to verify that it's reading the specific to their environment, let's put one
distinct property set.
For example, address dard dist equal to Distin so this property will read in the address service.
I will use the profile as there so that we can verify that it's picking up the profile specific properties
file and that's what coming through the config server.
So this is our local report.
Yeah, it came see at the service.
I wonder what properties this is in the local getable.
So that's fine.
If you don't commit live it like this, only it will work.
Now, let's turn to our address microcircuits.
This is the bootstrappers properties.
And here we need to define that which profile we want to fetch.
Basically properties for which profile we want to have so far that spring cloud, dot config, dot profile
equal to profiling in our example, it's do.
So this is the property you need to use sprinklered profile equal to do OK.
And that's what we have provided over here.
Hi Funday.
Our microcircuits ning.
I found out what properties.
So this is what you need to do.
Now let's read this property, address the artist, support that.
What we can do.
Let's have one day stepa in our address controller.
So we get mapping.
Celestis.
Public string dist.
So let's read this property in the address controller.
Add value.
This is the property and.
Private string dist.
Let's return this whatever property we are reading.
Yes, now we are all good, so you, Nagasawa and conflicts are really running, so we are good order.
Let's start the address service.
Until then, let's jump to Bowsman.
So this is the model for our conflicts are our adversaries, let's say profilings the.
See, we are getting the properties and this is what we have in their profile only address, not Istiklal
do testing.
Now let's see the address service.
So sless address and test.
So you've got the testing, that means a dressmaker's service is using the profile and it's reading
from here using the config server, so that's what we have.
This is profile specific or you can set environment specific.
So this is all you need to do, your microcircuits, name, hyphen, profile, do you know what example
and this is the property you need to set in your Microsoft Office.
So this is applicable to all the Microsoft offices you have here.
We just have a service as an example, but you need to do in all your micro services.
So this is how you can read the profile specific properties using config server, so that's all for
now.
We'll see you in the next lecture.
Thank you very much.