Hello and welcome back.
In this lecture, we will see how about Microsoft, we can get the updated value for the property without
restarting it and for that we are going to use actuator.
So first thing is we need to add the springboard starter actuator dependency in the palm cortex, email
address microsatellites.
So make sure you are adding the actual dependency in the Palm TotEx email for the address.
Microcircuits now lets them do the properties.
So here we are going to use actuator to repossess the property values, and for that we need to expose,
reference and point and hence we don't need to restart our microscopist to get the updated values so
far that we need to set when property.
And that is management.
DOT points.
Dot web dot exposer dot include equal to difference.
So using the repressor endpoint update to order, we will replace the property values.
Now let's turn to address controller.
And here we are reading the property, right.
That is addressed, the test using the value annotation.
Now, whatever place you are using that value, in addition to read the property on that glass you need
to use the notation is at a different school.
So here at a different school.
So this annotation you need to mark.
So here we are reading that this property inside our address controls.
So we need to annotate with ATRISCO.
And if you look at this annotation, then this is coming from the sprinklered config.
OK, so this is the notation you need to mark.
The first thing you need to do is add to the dependency and expose the rephrasing point and mark the
controller with a different scope, annotation or whatever place you are reading the property using
at value annotation.
So that's all we need to do.
Now our config server and unica server.
OK, so let's start the address service.
Now for this profile, this address, the testing will do testing value.
OK, so let's wait for the address to get started and once that get started, will change this value.
So let's see in the logs.
Yes, order service got started.
Now, let's take the test.
Yes, we are getting the testing value now let's change it to change the value.
OK, now we will get testing, that's fine.
OK, this is what we want to resolve using the actuator.
So what we need to do in our address, micro surveys, OK, this is the model of a micro service, a
product less actuator.
It's less rigorous and this will be a deadbeat matter.
You don't need to pass anything else, just click on the same.
See, it is saying that this property value has been changed to address the noticed.
OK, now let's hit this gate to get the property value that is addressed to test and see if our address
Microsoft is now getting the updated value or not.
Just click on this and see now we are getting the change of the value.
We haven't restarted our address microsatellites.
Still, we got the updated value for this particular property.
Why?
Because we have used an actuator and we have used the attorney for desktop annotation that is provided
by sprinklered config.
So two things you need to do whenever you have a change in the property, first thing is hit this post
you order that is less refresh on the equator and that will show you what are the properties for those.
The value has been changed and then you can get updated value, whatever places you are using.
So let's remind what things we have done in this lecture at The Dependancy explores the difference and
point and whatever places you are hitting the property using to add value.
In addition, use the reference copy annotation or that class.
Now, after that, whenever you have a change in the property value, the first thing you need to do
is hit the actuator, refresh and point as a matter.
That's all you need to do.
After that, your micro service will get updated value for whatever properties you have changed up here.
We just changed one property value.
But if you change the multiple property values, that will be also get considered and your MIKOLA service
will get the updated value for all the properties.
Here, just for example, we took one property value, but this is applicable to multiple properties
as well.
You can change values for your multiple properties in one shot and then it does represent point that's
completely fine.
Actuator will work and you will get the updated property values for Microsoft's.
So this is how our micro surveys can get the updated value of property without restarting it using actuator,
so that's all for now.
We'll see you in the next lecture.
Thank you very much.