Hello and welcome back for the upcoming lectures.
We will see how to use sprinklered open FEEN in the student service to make the rest calls to address
service.
So let's start by adding the sprinklered open-faced dependancy in the bombed out Zemel of student service.
Now, here we are going to use the spring cloud Vasan as three zero one.
This is the letters were done when I'm recording this lecture.
Whatever letters Vasan is available for you when you are watching this lecture, you can go for it in
this schools.
Whatever dependencies we are going to add for the spring cloud, this will be the version here.
I read it this vasan in the properties so that we don't need to repeat vasan in each and every dependancy.
And whenever we want to update Deverson, we can easily update by just putting the letters were sent
over here.
Now let's come down.
And this is the dependancy for sprinklered.
Open Feen.
This is sprinklered starter open-faced.
And this is the first entry zero one.
This is coming from the property that we added or here.
This one now, after the dependancy, let's create a separate package for the faint line, so let's
say the packages come in, people start faint lines.
Now, using this package, we need to enable the faint lines.
So let's go to our main class and we will use the annotation as enable.
Faint lines and provide the package, that's it, so by using this holiday season, we are seeing that
we are going to use the front lines in this spring season.
And this is the package that we have over faint lines.
So Fenland is basically an interface and that's what we are going to create in the next lecture.
This is the configuration part that we have done, adding the dependancy, creating the package and
enabling the front lines in our spring board application.
So that's all for now will proceed further in the next lecture.
Thank you very much.