Hello and welcome back.
In this lecture, we will create our very first open line to make the call to address service from our
student service.
So let's go for it inside this package, create the new interface.
As I said, our client will be an interface.
So let's give it a name as address fiend client.
Now we need to know that it with Ed Feen client.
And here we need to provide a couple of things.
The first is you are.
So this will be the you are telaprevir service that we want to call.
So in our case, that you are a lot at risk service so that we have already inside the application,
not property.
So let's read this property out here.
So this is the address you are in now.
The second thing is we need to give this client a name.
OK, say address, phone client.
You can give any name.
It's up to you.
Let me maximize this so that we have a better idea.
So this is our Fenland.
This is the you are to make the call, whatever it is, gatepost or put right.
This is the service you are in and this is the value we are giving the name to this client.
So this is one v. There is another way using the part attribute.
So what we can do instead of providing this, you are all here.
Let's remove this and just how the you are allowed this address service and here in our client give
the part.
Equal to this one, this is over, you are.
So this will be over.
You are not lot better service or whatever we want to call out and it will append this spot after that.
So if you don't want to hardcourt all the things we're hearing, the application, not properties,
you can put like this as often or you can directly provide the complete, you are allowed here as hardcoded
whatever you want to do.
Here we are reading from the application that properties just that you are an operator service and this
we are putting in the pot.
Now, let's move ahead and let's open the address controller.
So now from the civil service, we want to call this get by IDP's, right, getting the address by Heidi.
So let's copy this.
Completing from the air traffic controller and in our front line, put it like this.
Now, this implementation we don't need because here we want to call that grapey, we don't need its
implementation date, so let's remove it implementation complete thing.
We just want metter signature like this.
That's it.
Now, we just need to get the instance of this address being blind.
We just need to call this matter and it will call this gatepost the address service, because here we
have provided that you are a lot better service and we provided the party as well.
That is, you are right.
And this is also we have done get mapping it all and this will poza part variable.
So all things are done.
Now let's compare this with the address controller.
So here you see on the top we have this mappings Lesseps.
Let's address yes we have over here.
And the same thing.
We have this one to get mapping.
The difference is we don't have implementation over here.
And that's obvious.
Why?
Because every service will be having the implementation here.
We are calling the address service so we don't need implementation.
Does the matter signature.
Now, let's have instances of this address, Vinland, in the student service.
So let's autogiro here
like this.
Now, using this instance of a dress, being blind will make the gate call to address service.
So here, let me comment this out for your reference.
And instead of calling this get addressed by Idy, which is using the Web client, we are going to use
the open field.
So here we will use the address phone line to get my ID and pass the address I.D. That's it.
We don't need to do anything else out here.
Let's do the same thing in the getting the student by idea as well.
So here we are using the open phone line to make the race call to address service instead incident we
planned earlier, we use a.
Now we are using Fenland to make the race calls from our spring wood application.
So we are all set with our very first lined in the student service to make the right call to address
service now in the next lecture.
We will test it out our very first faint line.
So that's all for now.
Will proceed further in the next lecture.
Thank you very much.