Hello and welcome back.
Now we are ready with our very first feel, inclined to make the call to address service from the student
service.
So now let's run the micro services in our local mussy.
So let's start the student service and at the service.
Now lets them to Posman and let's call DeSapio to get the student body.
We got the response.
See, we are getting the address details as well, but now this time this address details are coming
using the open thing that we have Usrah in the student service.
This is what we are calling and this is actually calling the address service.
Using this, you are a lot better service.
And this you are right.
And that's why we are getting the address.
It is for that particular student.
So this is how we can use the phone line, the springboard application to make the rest calls to other
services now.
So, for example, you want to call another service.
So what do you need to do?
Is that just create another front line that is basically an interface or here inside the package and
do the mapping like this?
That's it for another Microsoft Office.
Or it can be any third party service as well.
It doesn't matter.
You just need you are all mapping and attitude matter like this in the declaratively.
So this is all about sprinklered, open-faced and how to use in the spring wood application, so that's
all but now will proceed further in the next lecture.
Thank you very much.