Hello and welcome back.
So now we are ready with the Eureka server and our micro services, so let's run the Eureka server first.
So let's start the Eureka server Springwood application.
Now, you need to remember this order.
We first need to start the Eureka server and then our micro services.
So what happens when you start your micro services, right?
It will read this property, whatever you are, you provided for your Rijeka server and it will try
to connect and register with this Utica's server.
So this is not running.
Then it will not be able to register with the Eureka server.
So after starting the Eureka server, let's start over student and address micro services.
So let's wait for them to get started.
Until then, let's go to Browsr.
Let's hit the Utica when you are.
That is localhost and eight, seven, six, one.
See, this is the judicature again here you see that what are the services and its instances are registered
with the Utica.
You see this address service running on the port eight zero eight two.
This is the student service running on the port.
Ejiro Ejiro.
So this is the address name coming from the application DOT properties file whatever we have right.
For the particular micro service.
So our micro services have registered themselves with the Eureka server, but look at this, this is
the Eureka server application.
This is not our Microsoft Web site.
But here what happens, Eureka server itself registered with the Eurekas.
Edward.
So this is not we want to have right, we don't want to register UDCA server itself with the Eureka
server because this is not the Microsoft Office, so we don't want to have Discovery for our Eureka
server like this.
So what we need to do let's go back to the application.
Let's stop all the services and all the.
Things including the Utica's.
Now, let's open the application or properties file for Unica server, and if you remember in one of
the previous lectures when we created this Eureka server, right.
I told you that we will come here back for the two properties.
And this is the reason that we want to exclude UDCA server from registering with the Eureka server itself.
So here what we will do, we will set the properties you record outlined.
Let's stop all the things, make sure nothing is running after you register.
Eureka, equal to falls, so this property we need to set.
The next is Ulrika Klein.
FEG.
Registry.
Equal to falls.
Here is the table, let's correct it out.
So this is what we are saying that don't register this service with the Utica and don't fit the registry.
Now, let's start the Utica server after that address my groceries and student, my groceries.
Let's wait for them to get started.
Let's go to Browsr, let's reloader Utica.
Address reservist that we see what the service is now registered with the Utica and we don't see the
Utica survey, so we excluded the Utica Sarovar from registering with the Utica Sarovar itself.
And hence we need to provide these two properties in the application or properties file for our Utica
server.
So this is how micro services will get registered with the Utica.
So that's all for now, will proceed further in the next lecture.
Thank you very much.