Hello and welcome back.
Let's have a look at the database structure that we are going to use in the upcoming lecture's.
So here we have one schema that is university, and inside that we have two tables, address and student.
So this is our address table and here we are having three columns.
This is basically the primary Geof address table and auto increment by my secretaries and other two
columns.
We have street and city now.
And another table we have is student table.
And here we have a couple of columns like Student ID.
So this is primarily an auto increment by MySQL database.
We have a first name column, last name, email and address ID.
So this is basically Fortensky and this is primary of our address table.
So here student is having addressed and that is the relationship between our student and address table
as of now, what the tables are having two rows in the address table.
We have two rows and in student table as well, we have two rows.
So we have two students.
And it's details in our database and the schema is university.
So this is our MySQL database that we are going to use in the upcoming lectures.
So that's all for now.
Will proceed further in the next lecture.
Thank you very much.