Hello and welcome back to Historic Steps, we need a right in this course we are going to use Posman
to hit the right steps.
If you are familiar with any other Esterline like advancer land or any other tool, you can go for it.
But in this course, we are going with Posman to hit the steps.
So this is the official website of Posman downloadable and according to your operating system and install
in your local machine.
After installing Posman, open it and you will see the screen like this, so here we can file recipes
for different ATIP methods provided over here, get pulled, forced and delete.
And here we can provide the URL, query bottoms and also we can provide the body as well.
That is basically our payload in the format of Jason.
So download and install the postman will proceed further in the next lecture.
Thank you very much.