Hello and welcome back.
So here inside this matter, we are making the right call to address service and on this matter, we
have used a circuit breaker annotation.
Now this matter, we are calling from two places within the same class.
So here are two different methods for creating the student.
We are calling this and while getting the student by ID, we are calling this method.
So two places we are calling this method within the same class.
As I already said, resilience for the circuit breaker internally uses Spring EOP, so here as part
spring, it will be concept, it will not work.
Why?
Because we are calling this matter within the same class so it will not able to create a proxy for this
particular matter.
This is the concept of spring.
It will be it has nothing related to resilience for the circuit breaker.
It's just that resilience for the internal uses.
Spring it will be.
So it's postponing it will be concept, if you are calling the matter within the same class, then it
will not work.
If you are of Arab Spring, it will be then you might be aware of this as well.
So here we need to do one thing.
Let's copy these two methods from here and.
Let's create one new class, see?
Common Service.
Annotate with a service annotation.
This two matters over here.
And let me copy this faint line into common service like this, and these two matters will comment out
or here.
So let's comment out.
Now, let me maximize this, let's all wear this in the student service, so here.
Like this, Ottoway.
Let's copy this Common Service, and here we will call Common Service to get addressed by idee.
So now we are not calling this matter within the same class, because now this matter is inside a separate
class that is common service.
So here we have this circuit breaker in rotation and our fallback method.
Now, let's say one Lowgar statement or case or Lowgar.
Lowgar factory.
Not get.
Broider class name.
That's it.
Now, let's have one count variable, OK, this is to count how many times we are calling the aggressor.
So say, for example, by default, the count is one.
And using this logger, let's come to this method.
So before calling the address service, let's log the count say count equal to.
Count.
Plus, plus.
And here we lock this acceptance or using the longer.
Ed.
Ed, equal to this.
Accepts a.
So here we are logging how many times we are calling the address service so that we can take the state
of the suite.
So this is for testing purposes and here we are logging the exception.
So this is also for our testing purposes that what exception we are getting while calling the address
service or when the suite is open.
So what we did is that we removed this piece of code for the circuit breaker because it will be will
not work out here and is already said resilience for the internal uses.
But it will be so we move to this piece of paper to another class that is Common Service.
And we added a few loggers now from front service.
We are calling this Common Service to get the address by.
So this is what all we need in this lecture.
If you want, you can do like this as it is and you can take it out as well.
This will not work.
OK, so this you can take on yourself if you want to take it out.
So that's all we need to do for our resilience, for the circuit breaker now in the next lecture, we
will test it out completely.
That how circuit breaker works when it will go to open, stayed open and close states.
So that's all we will see in the next lecture.
So that's all for now.
We'll see you in the next lecture.
Thank you very much.