Hello and welcome back.
So now we are all set with our resilience for the circuit breaker, and in this lecture we will test
it out, this complete thing.
So let's jump to Estess.
So here we will test out one scenario where address service is down.
So this will give us four four because I trust services down.
So let's start with the Eureka server first.
Then we will start our API gateway and we will start the student service.
So here we will not start the address service.
We want to test the scenario where the address service is down and this client line is giving us an
exception or error is for for.
So this is the streaming service.
Now let's turn to Browsr, let's say the Utica.
So now we are good to mainstream service.
We don't have a train service, so give a minute to epigastric so imposing a lecturer here and after
one minute I will resume it because we are giving some time to a gateway.
So here is the other lobstering service to get the student body and internally it calls the address
service and this is the actuator held wall where we can take the current state forward switch.
So let's say this.
You are on first.
So see the current state of the switches up, that means so it is closer.
So all the calls from student to address are allowed.
So now let me jump to Astiz and let's clear all the logs.
Let's say this, Gadsby.
Now, let's jump to his ideas and let's take the logs, see county equal to one and uptodate what it
give it give for four exception and that's why it is logging into our fall-back matter.
So this is the longest statement county called one.
After that we got four or four.
So it came to our fall-back matter.
It's logging the exception that are equal to the client exception that is for Ford and it's returning
the dummy address response C address service is down.
It's giving the exception.
But still our student service is not really.
You see, we are getting the dummy response or here podiatrists address it equal to zero students are
not.
Why?
Because when this is failing, it is going to our fallback matter and it's returning the dummy response
because our address service is not giving the response.
And here we are getting the county court to one.
Now we are considering last 10 calls.
Right.
And still our suite is closer to let's see the switches up.
That means so it is closer.
So this is second, third, four, five, six, seven, eight.
And let's take the logs.
Total eight now nine.
OK, all nine calls got Philidor.
And still, if you check then the switches up, that means which is closer.
Now let's make the tenth call.
OK, so once we hit that end call it will evaluate the failure rate.
And if it is greater than our threshold, for example, 50 percent, then it will make the switch as
open as per this diagram right from the closer to open.
So let's make the call now, we got the same exception now let's take the state of the switch.
See, the current status is now down, that means which is open.
So it will remain open for 30 seconds.
That's what we said in the properties, OK.
And if we try to hit the address service, let's see what we are getting.
Let me maximize this to show you, it is saying that Paul not permitted see, we are not getting the
council statement.
Why?
Because as of now, the switch is open.
So using this annotation, resilience, they will not execute this method.
And instead of that, it will directly call this fallback method and it will return the dummy response,
whatever we said.
And that's why we are not getting the count logo here, because the switch is open.
Let's take again.
Yes, 30 seconds, Capossela.
So now the sweet state is unknown.
That means half open.
Now, in half of one state, how many calls we are allowing, five calls we are allowing, right.
So let me clear the logs and let's hit this.
One, two, three, four.
So if we take the logs, 11, 12, 13, 14, C, now this matter is getting executed and that's why
it's making the count plus plus now the still the current state of the sweetshop half open, that means
unknown.
Let's make the call in half open state.
So total 15 calls.
We made it so far.
OK, whatever got over here and total 16 one in the open state.
Now let's take the current state.
Now it go down.
Why?
Because all five calls got filled.
So our failure rate is 100 percent, which is greater than our threshold.
That is 50 percent.
So from half open it will go to open state and that's why it's down.
See, so for 30 seconds it will be in the open state and after that it will be automatically going to
happen.
So let's wait for 30 seconds.
See now the current state of the sweetie's unknown, that means half open.
So here in half one state, again, we will make the five calls, but there is a slight difference.
So let me clear the logs in tears first and.
Let's sit this one second time, so two times it got filled, OK, because our address services.
Now that's fine.
Now let's bring back the address service.
OK, so let's start the service, give it some time to register with the customer and get it.
It got started, but still we are giving some time.
So now what we are going to do is that we need to go so far, right?
So another three calls we will make in the half open state.
So total five calls in one state, which we are permitting.
Right.
But now for three calls, we will get the response from address service.
Why?
Because just now we started the address service, so out of five to got Philidor and three success.
So the failure rate is 40 percentage, which is less than Twelver threshold.
If you see in this diagram, 40 percent is less than two percent.
So the switch will change its state from the half open to closer.
So that's what we are going to test it out because we are already seen from closer to open, open to
happen and happen to open.
Now we are going to check from half open to closer.
So let's go to Browsr and let's take a Paquita is working with a trade service or.
Yes, now it's good.
So this is one see, we are getting proper response for address, which is why because now address service
is up.
So let's go to student service.
So this is the third call.
OK, now we are getting done properly.
We don't see any exception.
It's not going into the fallback matter because we are getting the proper response from the address
service.
So it is returning this response only.
And that's why we are getting the proper address details for this particular student.
So this is the first call that is called successful.
Now, this is total fourth call.
So to got to got success.
Now this is last call.
So what triggered success?
Let's take the current state of the switch.
See, it got changed to up.
That means switches is closer, so 40 percent is less than 50 percent.
So that switch is changing its state from half open to closer.
And that's what we can see or hear.
Now, all calls are allowed from student to address service because of a circuit breaker incensing that
address.
Service has recovered from the issue, whatever it was having.
So it is making the switch as Clouzot That means up or hearing the actuator.
So here we tested all the scenarios as per this diagram from closed to open, open to happen and again,
open to open and from open to close.
Look, when the failure rate is less than threshold, whatever we set.
So this is all about resilience, where the circuit breaker.
Now, let's see when you should not use a circuit breaker for your micro services.
So let's take one scenario.
So, for example, our student service is calling the payment service, OK, while registering the student.
We are calling the payment service for the fees, whatever it is OK for semester or examination fee.
Now, this is related to money.
So if your payment service is failing, then you should not return the dummy response for the payment.
OK, so you should fill the student service.
So whenever you are wanting to have some critical data, you should not go with the circuit breaker
and you should not return the dummy response because it's not good for your application.
Now, if you return the dummy response for the payment, either success or failure, then it's not good
for your application because other things are relying on that.
Right.
You are resisting the student or for the examination or for the semester or whatever.
So for that critical data, you should not use the circuit breaker here.
It's fine because we are waiting the atrocities.
So that's fine if we are not getting it and we are returning the dummy response and we are giving some
time to address service to resolve that issue, whatever it is.
But this is just one example.
So you are calling the payment service, then you should not go with the circuit breaker.
Yeah, that's all about resilience for the circuit breaker in what, Microsoft offices, so that's all
for now, will proceed further in the next lecture.
Thank you very much.