Hello and welcome back.
In the previous lecture, we have seen what is a circuit breaker now in this lecture we will see circuit
breaker in context of micro services.
So in our example, we know that student service is calling the address service.
Now, see here we have one switch.
Obviously, this is not the electrical switch if this suite is closed.
That means all the calls from student service to address service are allowed.
If this switch is open, then all the calls from student service to address service are not allowed.
So if there is no issue in the service, the switch will be closer, if that is an issue in the service,
we will make this switch as open.
And obviously this is not the electrical switch, so we need to design it.
And for that, we need to define some properties.
And accordingly, this switch will be here.
So basically, we need to configure the switch.
So for this, we have a circuit breaker design pattern and we are going to use a resilience for the
circuit breaker.
So in the upcoming lectures, we will see how to design and configure the suite and accordingly this
which will be help whenever there is an issue in the service, it will automatically identify and it
will make this which is open so that all the calls from the student services to address service are
not allowed.
And by that, we can say over other micro services.
So in the upcoming lectures, we will see resilience circuit breaker.
So that's all for now, will proceed further in the next lecture.
Thank you very much.