Hello and welcome back for the upcoming lectures.
We will be focusing on the service, discovery and registry of our micro services before jumping to
that, let's first understand what is service discovery and why we needed.
So if you are having the real time application, then you might be having hundreds of thousands of micro
services, right.
And it may be possible that many of your micro services are communicating with each other.
It may be possible that one micro service is calling other five, 10 or 20 micro services.
Right.
It completely depends on your functionality.
Now, say at any point one of your micro services changes its you are in or the board on which it's
running now, that will be difficult for you because now you need to update that service.
You are all in other micro services where it is being called.
So when you have hundreds of micro services, it will take a lot of time and it's a big task for you.
But don't worry.
Here comes the service, discovery and Registry.
So sprinklered provides sprinklered, UDCA, with which each of our microcircuits will register itself.
So let's take our example student and address microscopist.
Right.
So this is Judicature.
It's a server and basically it's a springboard application.
Now, what will happen over both the micro services will register itself with the Eureka server and
while registering it will use this service name.
You remember this service name we provided into the application, but properties file for student.
We have given the name student service and for address we have given address service.
So Utica's arrival will create a register for it that this is the name of the service and this is the
you are allowed that service saying for address and so many whatever micro services you how each of
that micro services will register itself with the Utica server.
The key is your service name and it will be having your Eurail on Witchboard.
It's running.
All the things will come to your account server.
Now, in our example, student service is calling the military service and while calling it it is using
this you.
All right, this is the you are an op ed service running on eight zero eight two in our local.
Now, if you are using the sprinklered Utica, then we just need to refer to the service name.
So if we are calling the address service from the student service, we will be not referring to the
quality of their service, but we will just refer to the name of the service that is address service.
And the reason is that each of our micro services has registered itself with the Utica server and help
provided the service name.
So Unica server will have all the details that this is the service that is basically the service name
and this is the you are allowed that service for same for other micro services adversaries.
This is the you are a lot better service.
So whenever our micro services will communicate with each other, we will be referring to the service
name instead of you are in.
Now, this UDCA server makes our life very easy.
Say, for example, in future, this address service changes the board on which it's running from Ejiro
eight two two nine zero nine two.
We don't need to do anything in our student service or any other service.
We're calling the address service.
Why?
Because we are referring to the address service name.
We are not referring to the wall of address service that is localhost eight zero eight.
To know when we are working with Unica Server, we will be not referring to other micro services.
Biswal So that will be easy.
If in future any micro service will change its Eurail or the board on which it's running, we don't
need to do anything.
The reason is that it will be handled by UDCA server because it is having the complete registry that
OK, this service has changelog that you are on the board so it will update the registry.
We don't need to worry about it.
So this is the Service Discovery and Registry for our micro services and Sprinklered provides sweating
cloud Eureka.
And that's what we are going to do in the upcoming lectures.
So that's all for now.
Will proceed further in the next lecture.
Thank you very much.