Hello and welcome back.
In this lecture, we will create the Eureka server, so that is basically a springboard application.
So let's go for it.
Let's create a new springboard application and let's give the name as UDCA server.
Let's have this artifact, and this is the group that's change the Gibson and this is the package we
want to have inside it.
Click on the next now here, search for UDCA.
And we need to add this dependancy spring Eureka server.
Click on the next and finish.
So this will take a few seconds maybe to build a project and download the dependencies.
Now let's open up on a good example of this Eureka server, and here you will see the dependency.
So this is sprinklered starter Netflix's Eureka Server.
Now let's them do application dot properties.
So here we need to set a couple of properties, the first thing is bolt on which our Eureka server will
run in the local machine.
Now it's recommended to use the port as eight, seven, six one.
So let's set the port as Savol Dart board equal to eight, seven, six one.
Now we need to provide the application name, so spring application name equal to Eureka Server.
Now, here, we also need to add two more properties, but as of now, we are not adding them.
We will come to that part later.
I'm not directly adding this to because first you need to understand that why we need to add those two
properties.
So we'll come to that part later.
Leave it for now and open the main class of this Utica Castevet.
And we need to enable the Eureka server, so we are saying that this is not the normal springboard application,
but this is the Eureka server, so how the annotation is attainable.
Eureka server.
Now, we don't need to do anything else because this is not the normal Springwood application, so we
will not be having any of this DPAs over here, right.
So live it all things as it is.
This property is part we will come to later, part in the course up to two or three lectures maybe.
But for now, you just need to enable the Eurekas or the middle class, and that's it.
So now we are ready with the Eureka server, so we'll proceed further in the next lecture.
Thank you very much.