Hello and welcome back after having the Eureka server.
Now we need to configure our Microsoft offices so that they can register with the Eureka server.
Now for the Eureka server, we have used the Eureka server.
Dependency on our micro services can is client right because they are registering with the Eureka server.
So in the micro services, we need to add the dependency as spring cloud starter Netflix's Eureka client.
So we need to add for the student and address micro services.
So add this dependencies in the bombed out XML for your all micro services.
Now up to providing these dependencies, let's go to the main class of our micro services.
So first, let's go with the address service application.
And here we need to enable.
Eureka client like this.
And saying we need to do for our student service.
So you know what, you a server, we have enabled and enable UDCA server and here we are in a building
with at Enable Eureka Clanged because these are our micro services and this will register with the Eureka
server.
So in the both the micro services, we will use the add enable Eureka client.
Now we have defined that this micro services need to register themselves with the Eureka server, but
what is the role of Eureka server that also we need to define?
Right.
So let's go to the application properties file and here we need to set the Eureka server.
You are so using the property you declined.
Service, you are ill, not default, John.
And here, Provida, you are Elaph Eureka Sarwan, so in our case, it's running in the local Muzzin
so local localhost and the board is eight seven six one slice eureka.
So this is the you are Elaph Eureka server at the localhost eight seven six one slice Eureka.
Now let me copy this and put same in our student microcircuits.
So you know what, micro services we need to do three things.
First, at the Utica, Glen Dependancy enable the Utica client and third, provide the jewel of Utica
server that is running in our local Muzzin.
So now we are all set with our Utica server and Utica clients, basically our micro services, our configuration
parties ready in the micro services.
So that's all for now will proceed further in the next lecture.
Thank you very much.