Hello and welcome back.
So now we are ready with the Eureka server and our micro services.
So this is the faint light that we are using to make the call to our address service from the student
service to get the address details right.
And here we are calling by using the you are a laboratory service.
But now we should not be doing this because now we have UDCA server in place.
So student service wants to communicate with address service.
It should not use that you are allowed address service.
Instead of that, it should use the name of the service that is registered in the Utica.
See, this is the name of the address service address.
That's service.
So this we need to use in our line.
So let's remove this.
You are completely we don't need it.
And in the value we will provide the name of the service and this would exactly match with this one.
The case doesn't matter.
Uppercase, lowercase, that's fine.
Now we are good.
We don't need to change anything else.
That's it.
Let's run the unit customer first.
And then our micro services, so let's start the student and address micro services, so till it gets
started, let's do Posman.
Let's hit this goodbye to get the student body.
Just click on the scene, see, we got the response.
But the important thing is that this address details are coming from the address service.
And for that, we have used a paying client and we provided the name of the service.
And this is all working with the help of UDCA server.
We haven't referred to the You are the address service.
So this is all about UDCA server.
So whenever you're one micro service is calling another micro service, you just need to provide the
name of the service in your phone line.
That's it.
Rest of the things will work with the Utica server that will provide your micro service that you are
allowed the particular micro service, for example, in our case, this is the you are not address micro
service.
So Utica's server will provide this.
You are a little over micro service because in starting it will fetch the registry that.
What are the micro services registered with the Utica server.
On stratabound, each Migros service, it will fetch the registry from the Casadevall that what are
the micro services registered in the Utica server and its Jarrell's also it will obtain.
So that will help this micro service to communicate with the address service.
And this is applicable to your all micro services.
So this is all about service, discovery and resistivity, sprinklered, Eureka!
So that's all for now will proceed further in the next lecture.
Thank you very much.