Hello and welcome back for the upcoming lectures, we are going to focus on the distributor dressing
with Sloup and Zipkin, but before that, let's first understand what is distributor dressing and why
we needed.
So in our example, we know that consumate is hitting the student service and obviously it is using
the epigastric and from student service, we have a call to address microcircuits.
So here we just have one internal call between our micro services for one particular request coming
from the consumer.
But when you are working in the products and.
Right.
You might be having 10, 20 or 30 internal calls between your micro services for just one request coming
from the consumer.
Now, say, for example, your consumer is complaining that something is failing.
So how you will take that where something is wrong in your micro services, B, student service, address,
service or any other micro service because you have 10 to 20 internal calls between your micro services.
So how you will proceed, that is the issue.
Now, here, each of these micro surveys is having that logs, that's fine, but how you will identify
that these are the logs for this particular request, how you will track the distributed logs in this
micro services.
So here comes the slewed for distributed processing.
So what it will do is that in the logs, whatever we have, get logger dot info, debug Orara, it will
put the service name first.
This is the format it will follow.
And these three parameters we need to understand while working with the Slewed and Zipkin.
So the first it will put in the log statement is service name so that it will pick from the application
properties file whatever is provided.
The property we set right.
Spring dot application dot name the API gateways to the service or address service.
So this is the name of the service we provided in the application DOT properties file.
Now the next is Braeside.
So this site is unique for a request across all your services, including API gate.
We know this presider.
You don't need to worry about it.
Okay, so it will automatically generate it and it will be unique.
But for example, here we are taking the value of trace ideas, one for the one request coming from
the consumer.
Now -- the IP address will take that in the header.
Is there any value present for the residing?
If no, then it will generate the unique value and it will put in this particular request header.
So obviously when we call from the consumer side, there will be not residing in the request header.
This is for just example, am setting, but the first in the API gateways will generate unique to idea
and it will put in the refrigerator and it will pass that request to student service.
Now again, -- the student service will take that.
Is there reside in the requester?
Yes, that is right.
Even if the value this is just for example, I am taking.
OK, so it will handle and this is unique and it will not look like this.
This for the purpose.
I am taking the residual duty one now student service is getting the idea in requested so it will pass
the same to address service while calling it so IT service will also get that reside in the requester.
So slewed inside the address service will identify this tracery and it will carry on on either micro
services as well.
So for one particular request coming from the consumer place, it will remain same across all your micro
services, including the API Gateway.
Actually in the API Gateway Slewed will generate electricity and it will put in the requisite header
and then it will pass to other micro services because at the request we are not passing any trace in
the requested it.
OK, now spon.
It is unique for a request within the same MICROS service.
So here you see the sponsored CO two S1 for example.
OK, again, it will be handled by Sloup and it will be unique for a particular micro service.
So here we are just talking about the one request coming from the consumer, but it is applicable to
all the requests coming from the consumer.
It's just that I'm taking one single request as an example that is coming from the consumer.
So here in the gateway, gateway slipped under the spotlight, so it will be unique in this particular
Microsoft Office only it will not carry forward to other services.
Again, split in the service will create a unique opportunity for this particular request in this to
run service.
Same for address services, for example, is the value.
So this is the same across all your micro services, along with the Gateway Spaniard's theme within
the SeaMicro service set, for example, in the student service.
For this particular request, we are calling for different methods and and each of this matter is having
some log statements.
It can be longboarding for debug or whatever.
Now, how you will identify that this logs are for same request only that came from the consumer.
That is basically one single request from the consumer.
So you will take the sponte if all log statements are having the same sponte, that means this all logs
belongs to one particular request that is coming from the consumer.
And this is within the student service.
If you want to press the request across all the micro services, you will use electricity.
But if you want to press down the request within the service, then you will use sponte.
So service Ning Présidente sponsored.
So all these three things will be handled by slewed.
We don't need to worry about it, ok.
Regarding the uniqueness and all presidents sponsored will be generated by slewed and that will be unique.
But you need to understand when to use it and when to use cyanide to trace down the request.
Now, these things we can see in the logs, that's fine, but what if we want to check all these things
in the GraphicLy?
That means a dashboard we want to have or you can say we want to have UI user interface.
So that comes the zipkin.
So Zipkin is providing one server where we can take all these things in graphical.
We basically it is providing a UI tool so that we can take all these things to complete plew that this
request is going to run service and from there it's going to enter address service and where it is feeling
so smooth and Zipkin will work together.
So this logs, whatever slewed is generating right.
It will pass these logs to Dippin Server.
So all these logs that sleuthed is managing right to service them.
Trace evidence Monetti that it will pass to Zipkin server and using Zipkin UI we can check all these
things in UI.
Basically in the dashboard we can see that.
OK, consumate is it in the student service and that is going by IP.
I get to and from there it is going to address service.
So distributed trussing we can add to using the Sloup and then we can see in the graphical way easy
zipkin.
So this is the distributor trussing, and that's what we are going to achieve in the upcoming lectors
using Slewed and Zipkin, so that's all for now.
We'll see you in the next lecture.
Thank you very much.