Hello and welcome back.
In this lecture, we will configure slewed.
Now, in our case, we have logs in our micro services and also we have logs in API Gateway application,
but we don't have any logs in Eureka server.
So basically we want to trace our request in our micro services as well as in API Gateway.
So we need to add the dependency in our micro services along with API Gateway application.
So that's what we are going to do in this lecture.
So here is the slewed dependency that is sprinklered starter sleuth.
So we need to add this dependency in our address service.
Also, we need to add this dependency on our student service as well as in our API Gateway application.
So make sure you are adding dependency in all your micro services along with the API Gateway application.
We don't need to add this in our Eureka server now for our micro services.
We don't need to do anything apart from adding the dependency, but for our API gateway, we just need
to do one configuration in our application properties file.
So let's turn to the application properties for our gateway.
And here we need to set one property for slewed and that is spring dot, slewed dot reactor instrumentation
type.
And here we need to satyrs decorate on each.
That's it.
So this is just required for our API Gateway application only.
We don't need to add this dependency for our micro services.
So make sure apart from adding the dependencies, you are adding this property in your application.
DOT properties file for API Gateway application and this is just required for our API Gateway application.
We don't need to add this dependency for micro services.
So these are the things we need to do to configure slewed now just for testing purpose.
I waited one long statement inside this metal of student service class.
It's just a simple statement that it is inside the students get by ID.
This is simple long statement.
I read it for testing purposes only.
So now we are ready with the slewed.
We have done the configuration.
So in the next lecture we will test it out.
Slewed.
So that's all for now.
We'll see you in the next lecture.
Thank you very much.