Hello and welcome back.
In this lecture, we will download and install Zipkin server local Muzzin and also we will configure
our Micro Services and API Gateway so that we can use Zipkin to download the Zipkin server.
Just go to Google and search for download Zipkin server.
Open this one, QuickStart, this is the official website of Zipkin, that is Zipkin that will come
down and here you will see the letters released.
So this is basically jar file.
So download the latest version and we need to run that jar file using the dollar document.
OK, so I'm already having the latest version.
Let me go over there now.
Open the common room and run the javal, so this will start the Zipkin server in our local Muzzin and
that will get started on point nine for double one.
See, Zipkin Saval started on nine four, double one taught in our local machine, let's go to Browsr
and local host.
Nine four one one hit this.
So this is the user interface provided by Zipkin, and here we can provide electricity to trace down
the request, but this part will come in the next lecture.
For now, we need to configure our micro services and API Gateway with Sipkin so that they can pass
the service name to this idea in Spanish to the server.
So lets them do this.
So the first thing we need to do is we need to add this dependency that is sprinklered, sleuthed Zipkin.
So we need to add this dependency in our student service also in our address service.
And in our gateway, so make sure you are adding this dependancy to your micro services and a gateway
as well.
Now, the next thing we need to do is we need to provide the Zipkin server.
You are a micro services and API application so that they can pass the service name Tayside sponsored
to Zipkin server software that lets them do applications or properties.
So this is the student service and here we need to sell the property as spring dot.
Zipkin and besuited, so that is.
Localhost nine four, double one, so this is the default, you are Zipkin Zabar, you can take it out
of here, OK, this is the default one and still we are providing over here.
Why?
Because in future, if you want to run the Zipkin server on different board, for example, nine five,
double one, then you will know that this is the property you need to set.
Now, let me copy this and let's jump to.
All right, reservists and saying we need to provide EPA gateway application, so that's all we need
to do to configure Zipkin, our micro services and EPA Gateway.
So using this URL and using this dependency, Sloup and Zipkin will work together and whatever to decide
and sponsored slewed will generate it will pass that Zipkin server.
We don't need to worry about it and Zipkin will work together internally and Slewed will pass the application
named President Spinetta to Sipkin Server that is running in our local machine on board ninefold double
one and the other will be provided for here.
So let's recap the things.
What we did so far in this lecture we downloaded.
Does it concern that is basically executable javal within that javal so Zipkin started on the Port nine
11.
So this is a Zipkin server and in the next lecture we will see this part.
We added the dependencies Zipkin in our Micro Services and API Gateway and also we provided that you
are a lot Zipkin server, Kovar Micro Services and Epper Gateway.
So these are the things we need to do to configure Zipkin in our micro services and API Gateway.
Now we are all set with Zipkin so that we will test it out in the next lecture.
So that's all for now.
We'll see you in the next lecture.
Thank you very much.